export const x = {"easy":{"0":{"question":"000000000000000000000030000205046780340897100807051000051703090072900350938012074","answer":"123475968769128543584639217215346789346897125897251436451763892672984351938512674"},"1":{"question":"800702930020050000070008020004006009000001206600247051401600890702004010005073060","answer":"846712935123459678579368124214536789357891246698247351431625897762984513985173462"},"2":{"question":"000020000234070509000006000123060800400089003090210456340097600070630940900000705","answer":"615924378234178569789356124123465897456789213897213456341597682578632941962841735"},"3":{"question":"054908000000005009709100005002007608465380107807610400501700000008020900900860072","answer":"254938716186275349739146285312457698465389127897612453521793864678524931943861572"},"4":{"question":"000000030000100400680300100000056000406789003897200506310675000070000001904831002","answer":"149527638723168495685394127231456879456789213897213546312675984578942361964831752"},"5":{"question":"804000032000000000009100008210300800006890010700210046030062900561980020980701500","answer":"854679132123458679679123458215346897346897215798215346437562981561984723982731564"},"6":{"question":"000007500200156089508230006103400807400700003000002005042601000705980021080020604","answer":"619847532234156789578239146123465897456798213897312465342671958765984321981523674"},"7":{"question":"000090000005208000009100040200007900000089000007612054321074590564923080008060402","answer":"412795863635248179789136245246357918153489627897612354321874596564923781978561432"},"8":{"question":"000000300003000780059000000004500000000000200708620513530842961040013805981000430","answer":"276189354413256789859437126324571698165398247798624513537842961642913875981765432"},"9":{"question":"000024007020078009678059024000405090000007200000210506300500902002901005905702600","answer":"139624857524178369678359124213465798456897213897213546341586972762931485985742631"},"10":{"question":"005010300103057000080030000000000098050000010000124536030002967568070003972043800","answer":"625819374143257689789436125214365798356798412897124536431582967568971243972643851"},"11":{"question":"002004000000009050680050100210465009405008010807120006021806090040000870000001623","answer":"152384967734619258689257134213465789465798312897123546321876495546932871978541623"},"12":{"question":"000000000100257089009030040012400006405389002000012000020000060743006521006021030","answer":"258964173134257689679138245312475896465389712897612354521743968743896521986521437"},"13":{"question":"007000003003006000400070120014500098360000270098064010032800967870600400000000030","answer":"627189543153426789489375126214537698365918274798264315532841967871693452946752831"},"14":{"question":"000000000200100007700056000003460089407090005598703006010000008040932671906008002","answer":"651247893234189567789356124123465789467891235598723416312674958845932671976518342"},"15":{"question":"000700000100349008780006200210405700000800360090037045500682007072900600064070020","answer":"345728916126349578789156234213465789457891362698237145531682497872914653964573821"},"16":{"question":"000000004140009678709046005302450860450698310600000050520003906000000001064020700","answer":"236785194145239678789146235312457869457698312698312457521873946873964521964521783"},"17":{"question":"000020000103060000000300000000000007300000004009001356531706942642900081097412560","answer":"458127639123869475976354128264593817315678294789241356531786942642935781897412563"},"18":{"question":"780000304123009000400070000204030780056097040000200506502901000641000050978000013","answer":"785126394123459678469378125214635789356897241897214536532941867641783952978562413"},"19":{"question":"700010043003408009050000000010350090005000012870000056531062980002080005900500021","answer":"798615243123478569456239178214356897365897412879124356531762984642981735987543621"},"20":{"question":"000001000004250700000009000000000008006008037809000415320080950640910872907605040","answer":"273841569194256783568379124712534698456198237839762415321487956645913872987625341"},"21":{"question":"005004093030100000000350100023075800400290017897000000041080906068901732000000480","answer":"715824693234169578689357124123475869456298317897613245341782956568941732972536481"},"22":{"question":"000000056120450009000370120200600890006090005780210003400002078000703040800041030","answer":"934128756127456389568379124251634897346897215789215463413562978692783541875941632"},"23":{"question":"802007005030009670070008200010075060456890320700000000000704006647000500080036042","answer":"862147935134259678579368214213475869456891327798623451325784196647912583981536742"},"24":{"question":"000000006005000400000057120120540708546000201790200504301620000800971005974030600","answer":"417382956235169487689457123123546798546798231798213564351624879862971345974835612"},"25":{"question":"090840037023560089000100056004306098007298014080070005700000902062000003000000000","answer":"596842137123567489478139256214356798357298614689471325731685942862914573945723861"},"26":{"question":"000049650000050700500200030000005890450090003706000405600014078040030000905600341","answer":"137849652264153789589276134312465897458791263796328415623514978841937526975682341"},"27":{"question":"200107006034060079070000023310540700460000030090000461000010980740080602080720310","answer":"259137846134268579678459123312546798467891235895372461523614987741983652986725314"},"28":{"question":"080000006000000000000000000010065007050710360096823015031040978840930600972081543","answer":"187394256324156789569278134213465897458719362796823415631542978845937621972681543"},"29":{"question":"000020000004000579000000128100050000000700200000293410040675002092830050875910630","answer":"587129346214368579936547128123456897459781263768293415341675982692834751875912634"},"30":{"question":"670384005000060000400120000204035000060090204007000006530070000740912803080400671","answer":"679384125123567489458129367214635798365798214897241536531876942746912853982453671"},"31":{"question":"080300012100008409006029070200506000365897024097000030030060000600950780900000205","answer":"789345612123678459456129378214536897365897124897214536538762941642951783971483265"},"32":{"question":"000000005024309600070000034210005809407896002008123050001500900060004000905000700","answer":"136478295524319678879652134213745869457896312698123457341587926762934581985261743"},"33":{"question":"010340007030157000500000030123005806056000072800020015000010960001004000982506041","answer":"218349657634157289579268134123475896456891372897623415345712968761984523982536741"},"34":{"question":"007143060003007089000200037214000098065000000798010350009600071641070000000031600","answer":"987143562123567489456289137214356798365798214798412356539624871641875923872931645"},"35":{"question":"000570000000100060009006000000450609400398200897012304000060928068021000002800516","answer":"613574892245189763789236145321457689456398271897612354134765928568921437972843516"},"36":{"question":"008090000030008079670100200010400890056000132090002400001873000064901380083504000","answer":"248697513135248679679135248312456897456789132897312456521873964764921385983564721"},"37":{"question":"060000015100400700050070200000060800000891020089720103530040078002080000006017302","answer":"768239415123456789954178236217365894345891627689724153531642978472983561896517342"},"38":{"question":"000000120020000079070100006000600897006800210089201003501700942600000085097400031","answer":"364597128125368479978124356213645897756839214489271563531786942642913785897452631"},"39":{"question":"070300420003408079000207000210030890000000000000004350000672084708940010902080760","answer":"175369428623418579489257136214536897357891642896724351531672984768943215942185763"},"40":{"question":"050300000003057600080020305204039700005001090897004000500840970040003051078615002","answer":"456398127123457689789126345214539768365781294897264513531842976642973851978615432"},"41":{"question":"401000000030040009000000024023405090540009230098207005010084050800070300974500680","answer":"451792863236148579789356124123465798547819236698237415312684957865971342974523681"},"42":{"question":"802701000000000089000300000000005807400879013708023064020510070501080000980632400","answer":"852791346134256789679348125213465897465879213798123564326514978541987632987632451"},"43":{"question":"780000400000400000000008000214635709305897200800142005031080907070000030000003050","answer":"782351496153469872649278513214635789365897241897142365431586927576924138928713654"},"44":{"question":"037200000000000000680157204003460007500710302706820040300074000870030600960500003","answer":"137246589425398716689157234213465897548719362796823145351674928874932651962581473"},"45":{"question":"000200160023000079408070200004000890059007600780002004000704000001620943040801006","answer":"597243168123568479468179235214356897359487612786912354632794581871625943945831726"},"46":{"question":"000000000105308600070000000003060790400091063869723400300002900002000347086034020","answer":"934617852125348679678259134213465798457891263869723415341572986592186347786934521"},"47":{"question":"002800000000126080000307000000400897050080200897000460034070000560040302000032641","answer":"712894536345126789689357124123465897456789213897213465234671958561948372978532641"},"48":{"question":"000000002000000000509030147214050780056007214807024035000500976070001050000703421","answer":"143675892728419563569238147214356789356897214897124635431582976672941358985763421"},"49":{"question":"080004502023568400007020008000356897000000100708041030030002000070900043942600000","answer":"689734512123568479457129368214356897365897124798241635531472986876915243942683751"},"50":{"question":"000007821000300000000120000200050008450090006000270154031700962000012080980005410","answer":"349567821125348679678129345213456798457891236896273154531784962764912583982635417"},"51":{"question":"000000170020400509600000230000005000000007410890214356530000981740980020906500000","answer":"459362178123478569678159234214635897365897412897214356532746981741983625986521743"},"52":{"question":"500000000000000600680200157000400890056098070008002305010706928840921003060080010","answer":"521867439734159682689234157273415896456398271198672345315746928847921563962583714"},"53":{"question":"080100500000060000400009000010000700065008214798214360030020900640970050809001030","answer":"983142576152367489476589123214635798365798214798214365537826941641973852829451637"},"54":{"question":"900600300000008000000000000014000007370091000689000503001900782742183060096572400","answer":"927614358163758249458239176214365897375891624689427513531946782742183965896572431"},"55":{"question":"090500000100000579007009068200056090300000420005900316030600080806093052002840030","answer":"698517243123468579457239168214356897369781425785924316531672984846193752972845631"},"56":{"question":"070003000120450089468100030210300807057000020680000153501640000040900500000500042","answer":"975283416123456789468179235214365897357891624689724153531642978742938561896517342"},"57":{"question":"000000056023007000000089100204000090365090004000104503031806902040013800900452631","answer":"789241356123567489456389127214635798365798214897124563531876942642913875978452631"},"58":{"question":"000034020100507009000029057210006090375200610000001035000002001000905863891040500","answer":"759834126132567489648129357214356798375298614986471235563782941427915863891643572"},"59":{"question":"900020000004000079007000000000050090059000306000003005040075000692831750075294631","answer":"913427568584316279267589143436152897159748326728963415341675982692831754875294631"},"60":{"question":"080007256000346009070008030003405000406789300798023060500600900800090003000034021","answer":"384917256125346789679258134213465897456789312798123465531672948842591673967834521"},"61":{"question":"002000000045029670000007120003006700006000001000001406031864590508902300970015862","answer":"712638945345129678689457123123546789496783251857291436231864597568972314974315862"},"62":{"question":"030620000000008000000100237200007896406801070890000105300000081682003704901000020","answer":"739625418124378569568149237213457896456891372897236145345762981682913754971584623"},"63":{"question":"205000640004000009600050023300046007406090200780032056003671080060020310040380002","answer":"275913648134268579698754123312546897456897231789132456523671984867429315941385762"},"64":{"question":"000900000000040679089256034003000807050089013007120056030070002600000345008030760","answer":"364917528125348679789256134213465897456789213897123456531674982672891345948532761"},"65":{"question":"290140007030057009008009020310475000400001073080900415000530900800700000005006732","answer":"296148357134257689578369124312475896459681273687923415721534968863792541945816732"},"66":{"question":"060038000000069500500040006003056700007800000698070000301684007005013600040720010","answer":"162538479734169582589247136213456798457892361698371245321684957875913624946725813"},"67":{"question":"060780510000000089780100006000007090406008120800002300500864003030900850070003461","answer":"263789514145236789789145236312457698456398127897612345521864973634971852978523461"},"68":{"question":"000000004030150000009000135103460009057801000098700000041600090860007342972500816","answer":"516378924234159678789246135123465789457891263698723451341682597865917342972534816"},"69":{"question":"000015002020000060000040130013056080000008213090020540531800974800004000904530000","answer":"347615892125389467689247135213456789456798213798123546531862974862974351974531628"},"70":{"question":"000000000005000000078140005200006097400807000080310006027080054001924703800030621","answer":"132568479645279138978143265213456897456897312789312546327681954561924783894735621"},"71":{"question":"700042000023000008060008230210635709300000600806420053502900860640000092900050000","answer":"758342916123569478469178235214635789375891624896427153532914867641783592987256341"},"72":{"question":"000008000230007089570009024023070000406090000780623010300780900040930050907010308","answer":"691248537234157689578369124123475896456891273789623415315784962842936751967512348"},"73":{"question":"045190000000057680009000000010000098000800006096004051008000902001002873970683504","answer":"645198237123457689789236145214365798357819426896724351438571962561942873972683514"},"74":{"question":"300905102100060009000000000210056708050000010000713204730604800842501060065000400","answer":"376945182124368579589127346213456798457289613698713254731694825842531967965872431"},"75":{"question":"000000038000008009060379020000005007000890213789000450001704905005016000043082060","answer":"297451638134268579568379124312645897456897213789123456621734985875916342943582761"},"76":{"question":"070160300020000079060300000000604800040090200700210030037006900601980742092740003","answer":"574169328123458679968372154215634897346897215789215436437526981651983742892741563"},"77":{"question":"300715000005300070070008000003056709000000203890003046501600007060900850004572361","answer":"348715692125369478679248135213456789456897213897123546531684927762931854984572361"},"78":{"question":"090000804204000509570000100000000098056890000709210460010604007800020340900700602","answer":"691375824234168579578942136123456798456897213789213465312684957867529341945731682"},"79":{"question":"460001090000060508000208100000350000050000004007004005031902807740603900082700063","answer":"468531792129467538573298146814356279256179384397824615631942857745683921982715463"},"80":{"question":"805070600100400080070208005004005090050091004068004300000080000500017023002603510","answer":"845179632123456789679238145214365897357891264968724351431582976586917423792643518"},"81":{"question":"000080002000006000480037006004065897367001020098720000630000008042070561975008000","answer":"716589342253146789489237156124365897367891425598724613631452978842973561975618234"},"82":{"question":"908123005100000789050080103004065000005090004080000000000042070642070500097531062","answer":"978123645123456789456789123214365897365897214789214356531642978642978531897531462"},"83":{"question":"000070194020009000000008030004030009000897000708000350000081940840923000061705820","answer":"385276194426319578179458236614532789253897461798164352532681947847923615961745823"},"84":{"question":"000035918020000500500107004200006709006000100098502306400001092050024000060873001","answer":"674235918123489567589167234215346789346798125798512346437651892851924673962873451"},"85":{"question":"000000200230108000070000008123400890000089310700312400000070980001003020060804501","answer":"814697253235148679679235148123456897456789312798312465342571986581963724967824531"},"86":{"question":"000000905000000008580007000103005800006092310790603450000580706807920503040730000","answer":"612348975374159628589267134123475869456892317798613452231584796867921543945736281"},"87":{"question":"000000000020300600080100045203008000507209010698013204351080000800970001002501008","answer":"436895127125347689789126345213458796547269813698713254351684972864972531972531468"},"88":{"question":"000009030100006089079230000004005800350800264900720300030082070586907003090603008","answer":"845179632123456789679238145214365897357891264968724351431582976586917423792643518"},"89":{"question":"040030060030000079609147005000450700406789123800302046300500000060070000070600054","answer":"742935861135268479689147235213456798456789123897312546321594687564873912978621354"},"90":{"question":"400000000000209070689347005003456700546090230000103000021075900000912000007634002","answer":"472581693135269478689347125213456789546798231798123546321875964864912357957634812"},"91":{"question":"084000005000050000000208000010300600346781590708000010001095820050100903967020051","answer":"284916735193457286675238149519342678346781592728569314431695827852174963967823451"},"92":{"question":"300700105000056700500009200210000800456897300089200006031000078040000020072008541","answer":"394782165128456739567139284213645897456897312789213456631524978845971623972368541"},"93":{"question":"800100070020000000067080020010004008000090015009205306400020907058071400002503801","answer":"893152674124367589567489123215634798346798215789215346431826957658971432972543861"},"94":{"question":"090030040100000080008100005004360890009780406706000100600500900840007312070803004","answer":"597238641123456789468179235214365897359781426786924153631542978845697312972813564"},"95":{"question":"340000000000000009009006205010457896460300127000600000000800963600920500938061700","answer":"341295678526738419789146235213457896465389127897612354152874963674923581938561742"},"96":{"question":"010009530300120079000307004123400807457800003000000415031000900004900000070506342","answer":"712649538345128679689357124123465897457891263896273415231784956564932781978516342"},"97":{"question":"000010000104207089079400023010546700000800036096700000600934000003000960085070001","answer":"268319457134257689579468123312546798457891236896723514621934875743185962985672341"},"98":{"question":"000000361000056080670108040000047008000890007700000134400005970800900006900710853","answer":"285479361134256789679138245521347698346891527798562134413685972857923416962714853"},"99":{"question":"030000000020000009670050100010400806046090310807106425000600000762910583000020760","answer":"431769258528341679679258134315472896246895317897136425153687942762914583984523761"},"100":{"question":"000005000000000078600007200210050709450801300000720050530608040708912500002500010","answer":"179285634325469178684137295216354789457891326893726451531678942748912563962543817"},"101":{"question":"610000090204060008000200006023056009000090002000300005301005900762930801085700040","answer":"618573294234169578579248136123456789456897312897312465341685927762934851985721643"},"102":{"question":"910507020205100670008009045000456000407090030000072051040620980000004010000903564","answer":"914567823235148679678239145123456798457891236869372451341625987596784312782913564"},"103":{"question":"700001000004008000000070130000065090456097200800100000340082060600000581985710042","answer":"729431856134658729568279134217365498456897213893124675341582967672943581985716342"},"104":{"question":"000200100003060000400030050214306897000000610608712340730005004800970063060803001","answer":"576284139123569478489137256214356897357498612698712345731625984842971563965843721"},"105":{"question":"400000008000489060000207000014530780065008240790004056040670803006905000900003010","answer":"452361978173489562689257134214536789365798241798124356541672893836915427927843615"},"106":{"question":"900000000200008679007249130020060090450001006670080405315874000700000000800000741","answer":"981637254234158679567249138123465897458791326679382415315874962742916583896523741"},"107":{"question":"409000632005106000000000100020450806000398210807002304050800970700000063061500020","answer":"419785632235146789678239145123457896546398217897612354352864971784921563961573428"},"108":{"question":"070000000200058600680207000020405800000000017098613050000704962007920543002030081","answer":"175369428234158679689247135321475896456892317798613254513784962867921543942536781"},"109":{"question":"500040003200050000600030005123060780008791006000080400005800900800904502972513060","answer":"517248693234659178689137245123465789458791326796382451345826917861974532972513864"},"110":{"question":"000000000230000000009030040100470006065300071798600403340091700017026004080000502","answer":"851964237234157689679238145123479856465382971798615423342591768517826394986743512"},"111":{"question":"000020060000008000060009208000306807008090610009400000530002046706013080890645001","answer":"985724163123568479467139258214356897358297614679481325531872946746913582892645731"},"112":{"question":"005080000120000000709000200204000098350098024097204036031000802502841070008000000","answer":"645382917123479685789156243214635798356798124897214536431967852562841379978523461"},"113":{"question":"000000300030260500567340100210056800400001063070020400021670080045080601800104000","answer":"982517346134268579567349128213456897458791263679823415321675984745982631896134752"},"114":{"question":"002070000000200009008000123213506090006897031700000540501762084820010005060000710","answer":"392671458145238679678459123213546897456897231789123546531762984827914365964385712"},"115":{"question":"050000000130267089600000000000070090065080702798610305300090000507006901900021050","answer":"852139476134267589679458123213574698465983712798612345381795264527846931946321857"},"116":{"question":"000000000003050009000009300215006098346700000809210030031600970602070013900030004","answer":"794823561163457289528169347215346798346798152879215436431682975652974813987531624"},"117":{"question":"064105000003007000070200100205046090346080210008500460400000000032071850057004630","answer":"864195327123467589579238146215346798346789215798512463481653972632971854957824631"},"118":{"question":"062000050100200600000460000000040708400000030000000514301604970740002861806100042","answer":"962318457134257689578469123213546798457891236689723514321684975745932861896175342"},"119":{"question":"294010070030000009078049120300050708006098200009003000000030860840001050967580300","answer":"294815673135267489678349125312456798456798231789123546521934867843671952967582314"},"120":{"question":"000000060120670400400000170010000890065000010807042036540700980030020701001480020","answer":"759214368123678459486359172214536897365897214897142536542761983638925741971483625"},"121":{"question":"090020000005060480600040235200000008056098300089210540500682004042000003907034000","answer":"394825167125367489678149235213456798456798312789213546531682974842971653967534821"},"122":{"question":"000000000006070000700040006003456700065090300897120560000964800600031925970002643","answer":"238615497546279138719348256123456789465897312897123564352964871684731925971582643"},"123":{"question":"000500070003060080407080006214350790065000410790000305039000040000870900800903600","answer":"186534279923167584457289136214356798365798412798412365539621847641875923872943651"},"124":{"question":"004000900000300600009000034203000860406000320000603005001582006078906000062704081","answer":"634178952125349678789265134213457869456891327897623415341582796578916243962734581"},"125":{"question":"009603000000000460060000308210007090075096010090010573006000042041930080080400031","answer":"429683157853721469167549328214357896375896214698214573536178942741932685982465731"},"126":{"question":"000873105000040070000000200013460089400000312007310400001080067564030820000621003","answer":"642873195135249678789156234213465789456798312897312456321584967564937821978621543"},"127":{"question":"740000905100009000500067034000070060057600000098200300002580090871900523905703480","answer":"746832915123459678589167234214375869357698142698214357432581796871946523965723481"},"128":{"question":"200040037034250609008360100000070006007008003009000400700504000843010002900082341","answer":"296841537134257689578369124312475896457698213689123475721534968843916752965782341"},"129":{"question":"000000020003000009070230006014356000056007004089020005001682000002973501800415032","answer":"145769823623548179978231456214356798356897214789124365531682947462973581897415632"},"130":{"question":"070000060000460080068009040015040008000298005089071004400002006756910032890650001","answer":"974825163123467589568139247215346798347298615689571324431782956756914832892653471"},"131":{"question":"040109000003000000079200000204000006050091000097000000030700050765983421981542763","answer":"546139287123857649879264135214375896658491372397628514432716958765983421981542763"},"132":{"question":"300915000050278300000006005000407600400089203097000451500000980030500710004000532","answer":"342915867156278349789346125213457698465189273897623451521734986638592714974861532"},"133":{"question":"000000300034006000670208145103005800406700210800012504002500000000024031900603050","answer":"518947326234156789679238145123465897456789213897312564342591678765824931981673452"},"134":{"question":"000070600000000080000009005020465090406790200089310456340507908002080000007000502","answer":"215873649974256183638149725123465897456798231789312456341527968562981374897634512"},"135":{"question":"000980002100300000000207034013065000506708203700100400300000008070030621002814300","answer":"435981762127346589689257134213465897546798213798123456351672948874539621962814375"},"136":{"question":"040500000100060008079200046204356700000891004608024005401000050700100093905070021","answer":"846517932123469578579238146214356789357891264698724315431982657762145893985673421"},"137":{"question":"000000000000079000780046105013050080005090037897600450000064890670900000934500762","answer":"146285379352179648789346125213457986465891237897623451521764893678932514934518762"},"138":{"question":"400002000000008000080007234000005000060009000700010320531706982870590000940020751","answer":"413962578257438169689157234124375896365289417798614325531746982872591643946823751"},"139":{"question":"000000001025340000009000004003470869056801300098000100530000406847900502902500080","answer":"374268951125349678689157234213475869456891327798623145531782496847936512962514783"},"140":{"question":"740000030020000500000200000200056780357098204008700000402005007860902450900043601","answer":"746581932123469578589237146214356789357198264698724315432615897861972453975843621"},"141":{"question":"390084507105000000670000120010470008006891200709620015500000900030900050000042831","answer":"392184567145267389678359124213475698456891273789623415521738946834916752967542831"},"142":{"question":"208000050004000009070060023000046708400890206800023004020034805040100002905002340","answer":"268319457134257689579468123312546798457891236896723514621934875743185962985672341"},"143":{"question":"576000002020069078000100006214605089007000060600200503030480020000910030000050041","answer":"576348192123569478489127356214635789357891264698274513731486925845912637962753841"},"144":{"question":"090800010034000089008049000000000896400300000800612340005784000007921400000000728","answer":"592837614734156289168249537213475896456398172879612345325784961687921453941563728"},"145":{"question":"000900000123400060789000100000037006050009407800004200008090041040010983901040602","answer":"465921378123478569789356124214537896356289417897164235538692741642715983971843652"},"146":{"question":"000000005105000060079408100013040009050800001090020046500780604800004007007605012","answer":"384261975125379468679458123213546789456897231798123546531782694862914357947635812"},"147":{"question":"387500000020378509009004370213000897000000123000000045600780050800900200900635000","answer":"387519462426378519159264378213456897564897123798123645631782954875941236942635781"},"148":{"question":"000000200000000080000240100000065798050700002007302406305000967082936001961004820","answer":"418693275239157684576248139123465798654789312897312456345821967782936541961574823"},"149":{"question":"070009060005346080689007040000000090406091030000200050531870000007002010900000873","answer":"374189562125346789689527341213458697456791238798263154531874926867932415942615873"},"150":{"question":"000000000204100780009348105120005890456070200798010056001027900060000000087001000","answer":"815792364234156789679348125123465897456879213798213456541627938362984571987531642"},"151":{"question":"407000068005000400009000230010400090046780312708200546000002904800500003000804000","answer":"427935168365128479189647235213456897546789312798213546651372984874591623932864751"},"152":{"question":"002085470300007000008009035000000008000091062009020004200008057080072640706530020","answer":"692385471351247986478619235123456798547891362869723514234968157985172643716534829"},"153":{"question":"090000000000300000500009030013080006406091300089603015000812900842007001970506000","answer":"394158672127364859568279134213485796456791328789623415635812947842937561971546283"},"154":{"question":"008000501000000008569008034003460700050897100090210056002081067600000010901000000","answer":"238649571714352698569178234123465789456897123897213456342581967675934812981726345"},"155":{"question":"000090000004000609780036040123005008000000300000302000300578001001900800978640523","answer":"516894237234157689789236145123465798465789312897312456342578961651923874978641523"},"156":{"question":"000100400100050080500079103000540000056308210709610304305004001090705840007021006","answer":"932186475174253689568479123213547968456398217789612354325864791691735842847921536"},"157":{"question":"000000000000100609789050034020060000056780200890012456300000060078600901061070325","answer":"614839572235147689789256134423965718156784293897312456342591867578623941961478325"},"158":{"question":"000000300100406789500000040204300807000090004098704503400602958065000470000000600","answer":"746189325123456789589237146214365897357891264698724513431672958865913472972548631"},"159":{"question":"900080070000000000078239106010006090305790204700002060591020000600001025000900031","answer":"956184372123567489478239156214356798365798214789412563591623847637841925842975631"},"160":{"question":"260000000100000460009000000300047000000100300097360014501034090648971005073605841","answer":"264713958135289467789456123312547689456198372897362514521834796648971235973625841"},"161":{"question":"602079000130040009000000000003005000400090000096720415320587960561030782908000000","answer":"642179358135248679789356124213465897457891236896723415324587961561934782978612543"},"162":{"question":"400000002103000080069230047210300098300009214000120630000000071005910020981602400","answer":"478591362123467589569238147214356798356789214897124635632845971745913826981672453"},"163":{"question":"700300020003000007000060100004035080000000004897124000531406892000912500970800041","answer":"715348926683291457249567138124635789356789214897124365531476892468912573972853641"},"164":{"question":"300040000000007300600058120000470890000890037890023451000080900700032518002000003","answer":"318249675245167389679358124123475896456891237897623451531784962764932518982516743"},"165":{"question":"000200000034000000007000003100540607050701208780060510340020070670000802092070301","answer":"518234769934687125267159483123548697456791238789362514341825976675913842892476351"},"166":{"question":"004000690006000000009000200010000780000800025590703106600000050840510963975630800","answer":"124375698386249571759168234213456789467891325598723146631982457842517963975634812"},"167":{"question":"040020000000000700000309020200030608000100047780064503400072956672040031095000070","answer":"948721365123456789567389124214537698356198247789264513431872956672945831895613472"},"168":{"question":"000003040004000009500000000312400090450098000709312406000830970001070003003004861","answer":"127983645634157289598246137312465798456798312789312456265831974841679523973524861"},"169":{"question":"018035600030060078000200000100056789046890000097300500000604900064900001900500364","answer":"418735692235169478679248135123456789546897213897312546351684927764923851982571364"},"170":{"question":"300005000140009060700036200210000000406300002000012450500070006604000510938500724","answer":"362745891145289367789136245213457689456398172897612453521874936674923518938561724"},"171":{"question":"000725306020000079060000200200300097000090024009010000430001080670902403092003701","answer":"918725346324168579567439218286354197153897624749216835435671982671982453892543761"},"172":{"question":"090000000100000000067000103010540790456008200089010450031850940002901365075630000","answer":"398125674124367589567489123213546798456798231789213456631852947842971365975634812"},"173":{"question":"000094060200108350000306100100405000057010206608700415000007000004902571072581000","answer":"315294768246178359789356124123465897457819236698723415531647982864932571972581643"},"174":{"question":"042001300000060409000348125003006790406009203008103060301000002004012607007000001","answer":"842591376135267489679348125213456798456789213798123564361874952584912637927635841"},"175":{"question":"007093400003400009409070000204000000308700046796824001630502008800900020900607010","answer":"187293465523468179469175832214356987358719246796824351631542798875931624942687513"},"176":{"question":"004000002000009308080030000003400000460090210800300405530807604008940521940001837","answer":"314586972256179348789234156123465789465798213897312465531827694678943521942651837"},"177":{"question":"700293060204068579600450000000000090005700030897010045002000000000020006906831752","answer":"751293468234168579689457123123546897465789231897312645312675984578924316946831752"},"178":{"question":"508000007000070008070008000203040700406897001000010040041000002002901804905720310","answer":"528139467364275198179468523213546789456897231897312645741683952632951874985724316"},"179":{"question":"000000400000006009500047100200460800450109000090723010341600905805000041000004370","answer":"726891453134256789589347162213465897457189236698723514341678925875932641962514378"},"180":{"question":"900003040100207680067080123000500008406090230000002400020870005005900802009020010","answer":"982163547134257689567489123213546798456798231798312456321874965645931872879625314"},"181":{"question":"000040060000260009000000004000050800057801200090023405600500903745032081083604050","answer":"279145368134268579568379124312456897457891236896723415621587943745932681983614752"},"182":{"question":"000000001005200079009006000012007908400309007007012304521793400048000703003860510","answer":"264975831135248679789136245312457968456389127897612354521793486648521793973864512"},"183":{"question":"800000000000000009009130245210305800006809004700204036430627058000081070007043610","answer":"845792361123456789679138245214365897356879124798214536431627958562981473987543612"},"184":{"question":"087000001020000000409120307004536080060807124708014530006000002001050000040700805","answer":"687345291123679458459128367214536789365897124798214536536481972871952643942763815"},"185":{"question":"000100000020060400068300000210600807006897014780040350001000042600003701890410003","answer":"475128639123569478968374125214635897356897214789241356531786942642953781897412563"},"186":{"question":"000004070023507000400209130210630098006090204090140356530000040009001803040070000","answer":"985314672123567489467289135214635798356798214798142356531826947679451823842973561"},"187":{"question":"900000000000000000070200040010006097307001002600700315400675901005103600801942750","answer":"923418576148567239576239148214356897357891462689724315432675981795183624861942753"},"188":{"question":"700061090003000060600000000010030080306798215800125300001000900562000470908040031","answer":"724861593153279864689354127215436789346798215897125346431687952562913478978542631"},"189":{"question":"030018000004000070609007105213000089007891200800000000301002096502080010070036542","answer":"735618924124359678689247135213465789457891263896723451341572896562984317978136542"},"190":{"question":"040000800000000009609307105123056098456080000897203006012000000570602900060000000","answer":"241569837735418269689327145123756498456981372897243516912874653574632981368195724"},"191":{"question":"000080000124307689000240030213005008457801063600720004040000902000000046902030070","answer":"536189427124357689789246135213465798457891263698723514341678952875912346962534871"},"192":{"question":"805209000023006709000008020000500806350891074000620000501002000600980500087160402","answer":"865279143123456789479318625214537896356891274798624351531742968642983517987165432"},"193":{"question":"000203900100000008000000120014300009356800014098100300531040890062900000947002600","answer":"485213967123679548679458123214365789356897214798124356531746892862931475947582631"},"194":{"question":"000037528200140009678000000120465800407090000009002015010704000000010000790526080","answer":"941637528235148679678259134123465897457891263869372415312784956586913742794526381"},"195":{"question":"009010340100400080068379005200530600000092001095160030502000000000920810081703002","answer":"759218346123456789468379125214537698376892451895164237532681974647925813981743562"},"196":{"question":"000600000000078500000000007200300896356890002780000305630700054805903720072004000","answer":"197635248423178569568249137214357896356891472789426315631782954845963721972514683"},"197":{"question":"072000000104000600000109200200400007056000302789310065020080900690020703840936520","answer":"972643158134258679568179234213465897456897312789312465325781946691524783847936521"},"198":{"question":"000000000020460009500030140005046700000800625000700304031000057000953460006074830","answer":"164597283328461579597238146215346798743819625689725314431682957872953461956174832"},"199":{"question":"000094000145030080609100030203000890006879103090312000001000008000020000067581342","answer":"382694571145237689679158234213465897456879123798312456521743968834926715967581342"},"200":{"question":"000009008000100000089057123023046007050091230896273000002700060560002700970010040","answer":"741329658235168479689457123123546897457891236896273514312784965564932781978615342"},"201":{"question":"000100865020008409000009120210000700006097200709004350401000007600000540800041632","answer":"947132865123568479568479123214356798356897214789214356431625987672983541895741632"},"202":{"question":"000800000130000000009346005012400780406790030097103506021000807603082010040070050","answer":"265817493134259678789346125312465789456798231897123546521934867673582914948671352"},"203":{"question":"804021600000000080507009020000034800000007210089210006001502900650970431970100062","answer":"894721653123456789567389124215634897346897215789215346431562978652978431978143562"},"204":{"question":"500190300123400080009000000000000790350009064690704010401082006002903000975601032","answer":"546198327123457689789236145214365798357819264698724513431582976862973451975641832"},"205":{"question":"001030000234009060000056034020000000000098002090312006300680945006021800008043621","answer":"561834297234179568789256134123465789645798312897312456312687945456921873978543621"},"206":{"question":"030000570040207080009100034300405708007090020006072045520000060060903800903506010","answer":"238649571145237689679158234312465798457891326896372145521784963764913852983526417"},"207":{"question":"009184062100000000400209157010300000300400000806010004580001000037020840041803020","answer":"759184362123567489468239157214356798375498216896712534582641973637925841941873625"},"208":{"question":"070000841030260509500007200003056008056700123790012000020000900847900650000800307","answer":"672593841134268579589147236213456798456789123798312465321675984847931652965824317"},"209":{"question":"049000000100000000078009200002400790000090060806002014020003040000920851904705623","answer":"249537186135268479678149235312456798457891362896372514521683947763924851984715623"},"210":{"question":"400007000020000579508120300004350090057891460009200000000002900865040720000010083","answer":"493567218126438579578129346214356897357891462689274135731682954865943721942715683"},"211":{"question":"047100000000409008000000000000506000356700240098010065430025897862900050070800610","answer":"547182936123469578689357124214536789356798241798214365431625897862971453975843612"},"212":{"question":"000780360234156009670009105000465097006090000007000406300001908062008530900000004","answer":"519784362234156789678239145123465897456897213897312456345621978762948531981573624"},"213":{"question":"000100060000200079089057104210405008000000200000023010021700050500032781008016342","answer":"472189563135264879689357124213475698847691235956823417321748956564932781798516342"},"214":{"question":"060020950205000400000000100003040609040208071090360000002600094050914030074002500","answer":"167423958235189467489756123723541689546298371891367245312675894658914732974832516"},"215":{"question":"560004000100060000070100356200000000356090100800041503601050947702016030000403000","answer":"563784291129365478478129356214538769356297184897641523631852947742916835985473612"},"216":{"question":"040030006000108409000000100123506708450807001709003060002604080500081042890005010","answer":"941732856235168479678459123123546798456897231789213564312674985567981342894325617"},"217":{"question":"405000000030000000000030000000458000047300208698712453050004070060500934074683500","answer":"415267389739845162286139745123458697547396218698712453351924876862571934974683521"},"218":{"question":"000800075000240000678050000010070006000008700080012003020080960007901040800736521","answer":"249863175135247689678159234912374856453698712786512493321485967567921348894736521"},"219":{"question":"000000000000036700679000034200005090050780123798302406001670040004591072000004305","answer":"382947561145236789679158234213465897456789123798312456521673948834591672967824315"},"220":{"question":"004000001150009347000130006310006080465000003800002005021003004040000518070540632","answer":"234675891156289347789134256312456789465798123897312465521863974643927518978541632"},"221":{"question":"781040630000000000500300024003065800050800063608023051000500906000030510075012308","answer":"781249635234156789569378124123465897457891263698723451312584976846937512975612348"},"222":{"question":"000000000000000000060008123014000080006097200090024306630950807870203061900086002","answer":"123569478487312695569478123214635789356897214798124356632951847875243961941786532"},"223":{"question":"700020000104000000589107000000006708457000060608000154340080020072000610000012480","answer":"736529841124368579589147236213456798457891362698273154341685927872934615965712483"},"224":{"question":"000520040030000000000000020023406700457001000009200405302085904740902051905004032","answer":"671528349234169587598347126123456798457891263869273415312685974746932851985714632"},"225":{"question":"000300010100000000400100235000030000057802100009710052030085964862000573900603021","answer":"576328419123459687498167235214536798357892146689714352731285964862941573945673821"},"226":{"question":"000000000020300000679058103203506000460801235005003400530080900000035800986004050","answer":"354127689128369547679458123213546798467891235895273416531682974742935861986714352"},"227":{"question":"019720346230000000067049020100000897400800003708200065040000002601930000902080030","answer":"819725346234168579567349128123456897456897213798213465345671982681932754972584631"},"228":{"question":"207000008100000400080140005002456700450700103700302040020870004874001000963500001","answer":"247635918135289467689147235312456789456798123798312546521873694874961352963524871"},"229":{"question":"006000103100400009008009006000300790000000000689014025001003057705640832802005604","answer":"926587143173462589548139276214356798357298461689714325461823957795641832832975614"},"230":{"question":"040897031035200000080100200302400097007000020000000300021000970873000000964570012","answer":"246897531135246789789135246312458697457369128698712354521684973873921465964573812"},"231":{"question":"000000200120500489450200100200030000308000004579008360600820007002050041905106000","answer":"896341275123567489457289136214635798368792514579418362631824957782953641945176823"},"232":{"question":"010097320000000579709230000000000007507009061600000405301900002860000014074020053","answer":"415697328236148579789235146123456897547389261698712435351964782862573914974821653"},"233":{"question":"306000090000009060080346020103458679457600000608270000001004902860015040900000500","answer":"316527894245189367789346125123458679457691238698273451531764982862915743974832516"},"234":{"question":"001908657006100409080050100000009768405780000807200010010000000070002005000005241","answer":"241938657356127489789456123123549768465781392897263514512394876674812935938675241"},"235":{"question":"000003052005140000009050000120065080056008203890002065341007806500900307078000001","answer":"614873952235149678789256134123465789456798213897312465341527896562981347978634521"},"236":{"question":"284009060100040009070000240312400098450090020700002450500080970067004000943700010","answer":"284579163135246789679138245312457698456891327798362451521683974867914532943725816"},"237":{"question":"000008000100007509608000234000000800000801302097000140042716050780002460060580720","answer":"529348617134267589678159234213475896456891372897623145342716958785932461961584723"},"238":{"question":"900000000104000000008000100213000006050091037780063001001005072602034010805700304","answer":"927158643164329785538476129213547896456891237789263451341685972672934518895712364"},"239":{"question":"000060000000007080009000100215300090347891526060070304400785060590614807000900050","answer":"783169245154237689629458173215346798347891526968572314431785962592614837876923451"},"240":{"question":"000605032000000009000000040210050008006097004090000356401762005670981400002503071","answer":"149675832327814569568239147213456798856397214794128356431762985675981423982543671"},"241":{"question":"908005010103008500400020078200300807005090004709204005530040006000000750007503200","answer":"978635412123478569456129378214356897365897124789214635531742986642981753897563241"},"242":{"question":"000084000000000000070009300014630700056700014789040000030806007641900035097453001","answer":"123584976965327148478169352214635789356798214789241563532816497641972835897453621"},"243":{"question":"609000000020400080000030000200006790300801420005070000001080900006013852982745613","answer":"649528137123467589758139246214356798367891425895274361531682974476913852982745613"},"244":{"question":"000000006020609000000400020204500780006097200000000000431200097762003040985714600","answer":"149325876528679413673481925294536781316897254857142369431268597762953148985714632"},"245":{"question":"000170000103000670000068005204085700300091000090020350500846900086012003002507816","answer":"658173294123459678479268135214385769365791482897624351531846927786912543942537816"},"246":{"question":"000700040023400000000180000200300897306090004008010306000542008842901000900600412","answer":"189723645523469781467185239214356897356897124798214356631542978842971563975638412"},"247":{"question":"005000207000050009780230105004305098306000400800000006408072000502940000000003524","answer":"615894237243157689789236145124365798396718452857429316438572961562941873971683524"},"248":{"question":"605000108100500000009107006004006000006000204008204500507000680840000930960035740","answer":"625349178173568429489127356214756893756983214398214567537491682841672935962835741"},"249":{"question":"940800100000009600000005240210400000406000000789312065301074900004983701800001530","answer":"942867153135249678678135249213456897456798312789312465321574986564983721897621534"},"250":{"question":"706000200003000089009100340004305090300000060600714520030002608800640900065871032","answer":"746938215123456789589127346214365897357289164698714523431592678872643951965871432"},"251":{"question":"250060890340080000000030000100000709465090000090002400502043978630070020908020034","answer":"251764893346189257789235146123456789465897312897312465512643978634978521978521634"},"252":{"question":"010000006030007000000040000100056008000091000869023000341078952580004607706500041","answer":"214389576935267184678145329123456798457891263869723415341678952582914637796532841"},"253":{"question":"300200005020000000680400003010006080400008231000023040502614970007005000960872350","answer":"374261895125389467689457123213546789456798231798123546532614978847935612961872354"},"254":{"question":"000040000020009460000000000000000780306008004097402356000070092648901503972835601","answer":"165247938723189465489356127214563789356798214897412356531674892648921573972835641"},"255":{"question":"030007500000069478000008103000006709000800361800070045302600010761025804080000002","answer":"438217596125369478679458123213546789547892361896173245352684917761925834984731652"},"256":{"question":"007000000000000000080207100103405090400080207000610354301506002005001043902830001","answer":"217359486534168729689247135123475698456983217798612354341596872865721943972834561"},"257":{"question":"008501006023007080006000000010605000060098214000042035031800060002953871000016003","answer":"798521346123467589456389127214635798365798214879142635531874962642953871987216453"},"258":{"question":"900000000003007509000009024010030790356098201780000356031085007500900802092600005","answer":"925864173643127589178359624214536798356798241789412356431285967567941832892673415"},"259":{"question":"000032547030000080000000003003506000006798200009213400302000970000000312905301060","answer":"691832547234157689857469123123546798546798231789213456312684975468975312975321864"},"260":{"question":"042000000000000000000346120000050609050001000097603014324018950560032740071000000","answer":"642175398135289467789346125213457689456891273897623514324718956568932741971564832"},"261":{"question":"500000070030007600700100005000005000457800006608020050301580007806000513975030842","answer":"562348179139257684784196235213465798457819326698723451321584967846972513975631842"},"262":{"question":"000000304000020500709305026100056098060000003007203000502804000600901000070032641","answer":"251689374346127589789345126123456798465798213897213465512864937634971852978532641"},"263":{"question":"980200000030167500060409000103500090050700001090000640310050006645970002000021354","answer":"981235467234167589567489123123546798456798231798312645312854976645973812879621354"},"264":{"question":"000009000230008000009406103103040096450892000090300005300020080570000630908013700","answer":"614239578235178469789456123123547896456892317897361245361725984572984631948613752"},"265":{"question":"007000460120050789409000005000065800305009040698000000501000008700801500002500614","answer":"857912463123456789469738125214365897375189246698247351531624978746891532982573614"},"266":{"question":"810794002204000000000030000100065097057819203008020010000070908000980320900543670","answer":"816794532234156789579238146123465897457819263698327415341672958765981324982543671"},"267":{"question":"000705001000060009578100000010456008000891203609200000000010980045903002060082437","answer":"396725841124368579578149326213456798457891263689237154732614985845973612961582437"},"268":{"question":"000000000005037600700040105000059000407080090608070500530060907870910006964703001","answer":"316598472245137689789246135123459768457681293698372514531864927872915346964723851"},"269":{"question":"607090050004300600500007030010005000050010027790600140300580000802040513965700002","answer":"637294851124358679589167234213475968456819327798623145341582796872946513965731482"},"270":{"question":"040020097100079450670400000000006000300800000000100065431285970700903840080060501","answer":"548321697123679458679458123214536789356897214897142365431285976765913842982764531"},"271":{"question":"054102000100670400609008020000000709306000005798000300432061097507023040060704002","answer":"854132976123679458679458123215346789346897215798215364432561897587923641961784532"},"272":{"question":"002035060056008249089000100100400690040089310000010504030500786004020953070000020","answer":"412935867356178249789246135123457698547689312698312574231594786864721953975863421"},"273":{"question":"001000020000100000589040136100000897457800000006703415000600950000981302008530601","answer":"641358729273196584589247136132465897457819263896723415314672958765981342928534671"},"274":{"question":"040000530000000000080357120100475800000200300890003245000000002000034901968721453","answer":"741962538235148679689357124123475896456289317897613245314596782572834961968721453"},"275":{"question":"002703006100200570000000120013000709060897000090030005021600000580924300947381000","answer":"452713896138269574679458123813542769265897431794136285321675948586924317947381652"},"276":{"question":"831000046005100780670008000020000600450009000708300051307080902560090004080020570","answer":"831957246245136789679248135123475698456819327798362451317584962562793814984621573"},"277":{"question":"360000000105000680709020300010008090056009008007610052500700064670500901040801500","answer":"364985217125347689789126345213458796456279138897613452531792864678534921942861573"},"278":{"question":"000000000000408079450230000014306007300090045079824016031002050092040080005073900","answer":"968517432123468579457239168214356897386791245579824316631982754792145683845673921"},"279":{"question":"000032005000006089060470100023007608056089310790360250002090800000000900907620030","answer":"871932465234156789569478123123547698456289317798361254312795846645813972987624531"},"280":{"question":"009740830000000070070100050214000700000897020007200060532080007740005680980003510","answer":"159742836423568179678139254214356798365897421897214365532681947741925683986473512"},"281":{"question":"060040297020500000000260130200050089300091020608020051030600902042000016006000043","answer":"563148297721539468489267135214756389357891624698423751135684972942375816876912543"},"282":{"question":"000200500100000000400000000010300806365000472809620003501742960040008010080510020","answer":"693287541128459637457136289214375896365891472879624153531742968742968315986513724"},"283":{"question":"200000500145000009680300000010070090450080237008600000021704600073010942900802700","answer":"237149568145268379689357124312475896456981237798623415521794683873516942964832751"},"284":{"question":"000800000120050709508300000010037098050198047000064010431680000002900835900000461","answer":"679812354123456789548379126214537698356198247897264513431685972762941835985723461"},"285":{"question":"004079200025006700670020300200007090406892000000013052001000976000961003000735010","answer":"184379265325146789679528341213457698456892137798613452531284976847961523962735814"},"286":{"question":"007000001000067080060100000200050798450791306796200005001872050800000600000034812","answer":"387529461124367589569148237213456798458791326796283145631872954842915673975634812"},"287":{"question":"508160000100007689007080005200005896006090007000004300000000000872906513000008762","answer":"538169274124357689967482135241735896356891427789624351615273948872946513493518762"},"288":{"question":"060008000000009408080000200013457009046800000897060010000700906658003741000010020","answer":"362548197175239468984176253213457689546891372897362514421785936658923741739614825"},"289":{"question":"000032000023400000000180005010360798005208416698010050000826000002901000006003800","answer":"157632984823459167469187235214365798375298416698714352731826549582941673946573821"},"290":{"question":"000900200000000000409000050204350000065700104890240060538670940600800702072013685","answer":"153964278726538419489127356214356897365789124897241563538672941641895732972413685"},"291":{"question":"000030000030000580500400100020540790406708231790000045010054976600000812070601000","answer":"167835429234169587589427163321546798456798231798312645813254976645973812972681354"},"292":{"question":"000300005004050600060000030000075096050090300080623051300010960671984000890506700","answer":"127369845934158672568247139413875296256491387789623451345712968671984523892536714"},"293":{"question":"000703040000000009000000000000000807400070302700010060025684971841000653900530428","answer":"158793246234156789679248135513462897496875312782319564325684971841927653967531428"},"294":{"question":"000000307130060000600308005203406000006089013090123006300802004000035600057604830","answer":"482591367135267489679348125213456798546789213798123546361872954824935671957614832"},"295":{"question":"001304000004000000000058034003085090400090003098603410312806009045000026967002000","answer":"581324967734169258629758134173485692456291783298673415312846579845917326967532841"},"296":{"question":"001093000000000080060248007000456000056000312090000460318600074042070800075030601","answer":"281793546734561289569248137123456798456987312897312465318625974642179853975834621"},"297":{"question":"500000001000250000000100200003460780400090020000723004321504067046907000900602040","answer":"562378491134259678789146235213465789457891326698723154321584967846937512975612843"},"298":{"question":"000100000003060000468070000200056000370091006000407350000082064602905000987004012","answer":"729143685153268479468579123214356798375891246896427351531782964642915837987634512"},"299":{"question":"070040000000070000450009070010350800060097214790000300531004980047001000002560041","answer":"873145629129678453456239178214356897365897214798412365531724986647981532982563741"}},"medium":{"0":{"question":"000900560000000709000007030020000090000008013897000456312049600064000021908001005","answer":"731984562245136789689257134123465897456798213897312456312549678564873921978621345"},"1":{"question":"000090400000056009069000000000540000406109000000003500020004070740915862905000001","answer":"132798456874256139569431728318542697456179283297863514621384975743915862985627341"},"2":{"question":"000201800023000400008069000010000098007800000609007030730680000840900076005004001","answer":"496231857123578469578469123214356798357892614689147235731685942842913576965724381"},"3":{"question":"870600050000200000560000000010005080000890003000000400301080006680021040900006812","answer":"872613954193254768564978231219345687456897123738162495321489576685721349947536812"},"4":{"question":"000000000030000600000000105000000780000090200000010006300520090508971062902806541","answer":"124365978735189624689247135216453789457698213893712456361524897548971362972836541"},"5":{"question":"000005090000000000009140030000050080407090362000700004030600047700010850908500621","answer":"216375498384269175579148236621453789457891362893726514135682947762914853948537621"},"6":{"question":"900500000000007080007300024000000008300008005708100030430000900000943001800215600","answer":"912584367543627189687391524156432798394768215728159436431876952265943871879215643"},"7":{"question":"004000000023460000007009200000040090340007600079500300400800051000050402852910000","answer":"164725839923468175587139246218346597345297618679581324436872951791653482852914763"},"8":{"question":"506000007004000060000000000000500608000000000698103470000005980860902710972004056","answer":"516249837324781569789356241143597628257468193698123475431675982865932714972814356"},"9":{"question":"000080000004000000070000009012400007007308106680012000003605980000900002960820700","answer":"129586374534197268876234519312469857497358126685712493243675981758941632961823745"},"10":{"question":"900500040003000500050000200200306000300001026600274010506700080040980050092040701","answer":"927568143163427598458139267214356879375891426689274315536712984741983652892645731"},"11":{"question":"000000000004009000000000100003405089050090030708000015005704962002006053000530801","answer":"231647598584129376679358124123475689456891237798263415315784962842916753967532841"},"12":{"question":"000001008000000307700005000300006000400008003008023015521800604800910000074060830","answer":"235671948146289357789345126312456789457198263698723415521837694863914572974562831"},"13":{"question":"060007000103008000070120008010056897006009004800000000000400900000095631085630702","answer":"268947513143568279579123468314256897756389124892714356631472985427895631985631742"},"14":{"question":"902700010030200000000109000010465000000000100000000400320670958000000001897530640","answer":"942753816135286794678149523713465289264897135589312467321674958456928371897531642"},"15":{"question":"700030010100407509000120000015000000006700000097000030000072960001803000072014000","answer":"724935618138467529569128347215349786346781295897256134483572961651893472972614853"},"16":{"question":"080070000000308070000020008000056090006800013008200405530700080040900000962500000","answer":"184675329629348571375129648213456897456897213798213465531764982847932156962581734"},"17":{"question":"000104002000000000000206000000000089000800026608720000530040900800017603076038201","answer":"357194862162385497489276315215463789743859126698721534531642978824917653976538241"},"18":{"question":"054030000000070009000056003000040600000000370000062500021800706643725081970014000","answer":"154239867236178459789456123312547698465981372897362514521893746643725981978614235"},"19":{"question":"600800203000160070080200000000056089050000000008000060302001950800000630001573000","answer":"617845293234169578589237146123456789456798312798312465342681957875924631961573824"},"20":{"question":"002008407040000000000000005020000000000001000090302504230700956060920041074615020","answer":"312568497547139268689247135728456319453891672196372584231784956865923741974615823"},"21":{"question":"030745000004000000060129300000006097000007003700010006001070000005900000972581000","answer":"138745269294368175567129348413256897826497513759813426381674952645932781972581634"},"22":{"question":"098500620120000009400080130010300700000008200000000050007840962000030805000070403","answer":"798513624123467589456289137214356798365798241879124356537841962641932875982675413"},"23":{"question":"010607000004100000000000105023000000050091300800002451345700900760003500901524000","answer":"219657834574138296638249175123475689456891327897362451345786912762913548981524763"},"24":{"question":"000098070000350009000000005200005000400010300690700450300582000862071043900034010","answer":"523198674146357289789246135231465798457819326698723451314582967862971543975634812"},"25":{"question":"000000800000070000700050030010060000000819326000007045000601072860700450900043081","answer":"125934867346278519789156234213465798457819326698327145534681972861792453972543681"},"26":{"question":"000001000034000070700006000213400709050000200000103006301004907600007000970602000","answer":"562371498134289675789546123213465789456798231897123546321854967645937812978612354"},"27":{"question":"000004000004000079007100048300006807456000010009002050600040085800920630040085020","answer":"198274563234568179567139248312456897456897312789312456621743985875921634943685721"},"28":{"question":"001048500000150000080000004000000000400800300798020015300780956005000043947030000","answer":"231648579674159238589372164123965487456817392798423615312784956865291743947536821"},"29":{"question":"000000000040006000079000024100000890000080231008210400002004070837590000964870310","answer":"281459763345726189679138524123645897456987231798213456512364978837591642964872315"},"30":{"question":"870020000004060080500008000100000000400700001708010000000090870040831050000672310","answer":"871325469234967185569148237123456798496783521758219643312594876647831952985672314"},"31":{"question":"000000010000209000700000040200050069406091082097060104020004006060003807000600401","answer":"632547918145289673789136245213458769456791382897362154321874596564913827978625431"},"32":{"question":"006000490100060570070300106002000009457800000008103000020005030800900000065734802","answer":"236517498184269573579348126312456789457892361698173245721685934843921657965734812"},"33":{"question":"060020901020000000000060234004050080056090100000010050600740800000900600005600420","answer":"368524971421379568579168234134256789756893142892417356613742895247985613985631427"},"34":{"question":"000000095000000000070060100210075069056001300807003401305010086062984000900000002","answer":"128347695634159278579268134213475869456891327897623451345712986762984513981536742"},"35":{"question":"090000000000006000468300005004030006350108040000200000000040078000005903070683402","answer":"193452687527896134468317295714539826352168749689274351236941578841725963975683412"},"36":{"question":"006000000020400000070000034210375008050081207000904300430090086000003002802700500","answer":"146537829328419675579268134214375968953681247687924351435192786761853492892746513"},"37":{"question":"000000000020000009508009030004037806300098040700600051001860002002900500090002000","answer":"943786125127453689568219734214537896356198247789624351431865972872941563695372418"},"38":{"question":"604000508103000079000000100010004000000789005798200000030000900000041763907003051","answer":"624197538183452679579368124215634897346789215798215346431576982852941763967823451"},"39":{"question":"900071000100000570000030008004050000006090000780004035400002956670000483000003700","answer":"928571364143268579567439128214356897356897241789124635431782956672915483895643712"},"40":{"question":"300010908000000000709305106000406000005000210000103000520901600030500090900062000","answer":"342617958156289347789345126213456789465798213897123465528931674631574892974862531"},"41":{"question":"300002100106040000709000000000060890000700000000013400002094001001800025970520643","answer":"345972168126348579789156234213465897654789312897213456532694781461837925978521643"},"42":{"question":"000840000030100009000239040120050000006000230800002406312004000005900012007520300","answer":"269845173438167529571239648124356897756498231893712456312674985645983712987521364"},"43":{"question":"000060100020300070007140200000400000400000320098030015040007002000904500005620001","answer":"354762189129358674867149253532471896416895327798236415641587932273914568985623741"},"44":{"question":"759000008003000000060070030000050807000891200000007000530702960042900703900004502","answer":"759136428123548679468279135214653897375891246896427351531782964642915783987364512"},"45":{"question":"010000024000100080000200006000400800000000003897310405000001008000903001061084372","answer":"315698724246137589789245136123456897654879213897312465432761958578923641961584372"},"46":{"question":"002060090130270068000000000000000000400800000708000000300685970007932000986000302","answer":"842163597135279468679458123251346789463897215798521634324685971517932846986714352"},"47":{"question":"000030000204006700008000100000507000000000030000002005301600908602000041985714060","answer":"167238459294156783538479126823597614459861237716342895341625978672983541985714362"},"48":{"question":"000700000000000508009008030000075089465091020008000400006587940007002000902000751","answer":"851734296234169578679258134123475689465891327798326415316587942547912863982643751"},"49":{"question":"002608000130247009000000000200060000047000000000000400020586900750000860086700540","answer":"472698135135247689698135274219364758847951326563872491324586917751429863986713542"},"50":{"question":"000000008120000600000100000010405890000619300000023005001040900845932700960000000","answer":"356294178127358649498167253213475896584619327679823415731546982845932761962781534"},"51":{"question":"090235000030600000000049000003006000000000302009010450300000084017000003904503701","answer":"196235847432678915578149236253486179841957362769312458325791684617824593984563721"},"52":{"question":"007080000123000509000230047004306790350010000700020005430000001602000000891503000","answer":"547189236123467589968235147214356798359718462786924315435692871672841953891573624"},"53":{"question":"006000200000009008000006340003000000057690000000003100001700980802905030904832500","answer":"146358279325479618789126345213587496457691823698243157531764982862915734974832561"},"54":{"question":"000007004200000000000000000103000000008000000079083405315874062700000500986532741","answer":"531267894264398157897451236123945678458726319679183425315874962742619583986532741"},"55":{"question":"000000005020406000008200006000060000000098000000124063630040978040980651900000402","answer":"163879245529436187478251396314765829256398714897124563631542978742983651985617432"},"56":{"question":"000000000003058000609000058200005806356080710008004005001802067000000003907030001","answer":"185967432423158679679423158214375896356289714798614325531842967862791543947536281"},"57":{"question":"950000000130200070000000200013000007460000000000620015001040000047916820090002040","answer":"952187364134269578786435291213594687465871932879623415621348759547916823398752146"},"58":{"question":"000100300000060000000380100010600000065790010098241563030006000640000875907402000","answer":"856124397173569248429387156214635789365798412798241563531876924642913875987452631"},"59":{"question":"856009020120050000000068100004000090000801000000620000501700060000080000082506740","answer":"856139427123457689479268135214375896365891274798624351531742968647983512982516743"},"60":{"question":"030697004006100009000040006000056008400000000690000005000060000860070010004821053","answer":"132697584546138279789245136213456798457982361698713425321569847865374912974821653"},"61":{"question":"609000010000050079400060230004005000000091704800000000530706082742900060900000347","answer":"629378415318254679457169238174625893263891754895437126531746982742983561986512347"},"62":{"question":"000000400200007580700050020023009008400600300090300200010000957000005600960023004","answer":"531298476246137589789456123123549768457682391698371245312864957874915632965723814"},"63":{"question":"009020008020000009000400020010005000050000004000040306030050982002910740005084600","answer":"149326578328571469576498123614835297253769814987142356431657982862913745795284631"},"64":{"question":"009062000000000080006000107004030000060090040000204056008001902042000815901020003","answer":"189762534427153689536489127714635298265897341893214756658341972342976815971528463"},"65":{"question":"010000060040009570000250000023060000050000000008710040001624807860001400904583600","answer":"315847962246139578789256134123465789457398216698712345531624897862971453974583621"},"66":{"question":"500000300000250700000130000000000000450000020700002050005074908861020004000501632","answer":"512467389348259761697138245126745893453896127789312456235674918861923574974581632"},"67":{"question":"005049000000057600009000000003000000050008213890003006531002904048900030970000061","answer":"165849327324157689789326145213465798456798213897213456531682974648971532972534861"},"68":{"question":"002000010045008070000039040003050008000090020700000564520003907807920000000080650","answer":"392574816145268379678139245213456798456897123789312564521643987867925431934781652"},"69":{"question":"000000040020009070000100006000006089007001060608020050002604090000000610900578403","answer":"135267948426389571789145236213456789547891362698723154352614897874932615961578423"},"70":{"question":"704000500100500000000000020000306800000800000870000300400600900650982734982030051","answer":"724163598168529473395478126249356817513847269876291345437615982651982734982734651"},"71":{"question":"200100600106000050009050000000000000405300000000000040521734900678900034003065712","answer":"254173689136289457789456123312547896465398271897612345521734968678921534943865712"},"72":{"question":"904000000020000609000000000000046790346708502008002000400020007672000050859670020","answer":"964137285123854679587269134215346798346798512798512346431925867672481953859673421"},"73":{"question":"000000003000000089000000000004000890050891074090024305000700908000983502900046700","answer":"128479653376152489549368127214537896653891274897624315432715968761983542985246731"},"74":{"question":"000500000356170240000000000003000708005007310890010000502000004074900503930005620","answer":"241539867356178249789264135123456798465897312897312456512683974674921583938745621"},"75":{"question":"000170000000000000670000130203000090000791280090023000002006009005902841900500300","answer":"324175968158369472679284135213458697546791283897623514432816759765932841981547326"},"76":{"question":"000390050000006000560008020010000000006080000000600514001030900700905060980760301","answer":"247391658198256437563478129312549786456187293879623514621834975734915862985762341"},"77":{"question":"000000000024000600008100037010000890050091070080000004600004005005912700900530008","answer":"397265481124378659568149237213457896456891372789623514631784925845912763972536148"},"78":{"question":"800000200004008009060000000000000800006800002790002406342071085605023040901504000","answer":"817395264534268719269417538423756891156849372798132456342671985685923147971584623"},"79":{"question":"300070100000006789500180200000000000000718326000000400000000978000007013075001042","answer":"389274165142356789567189234613425897954718326728693451431562978296847513875931642"},"80":{"question":"008004050000000000000000000000000000000091000080603415635012948071040503040538061","answer":"128374659354169287796285134412857396563491872987623415635712948871946523249538761"},"81":{"question":"310205090040060308000000100020056000000790200700000400000600900062904007970002860","answer":"317285694245169378689347125123456789458791236796823451531678942862934517974512863"},"82":{"question":"000600400103000670060000000210000897006000000890014356035040900040900060002036001","answer":"578621439123459678469873125214365897356798214897214356635147982741982563982536741"},"83":{"question":"000070130020450000508100006000005800007298001000010350730000920860020500000507013","answer":"496872135123456789578139246214365897357298461689714352735641928861923574942587613"},"84":{"question":"040000000000000008079008000000075809000001000790024300430087000000900481082046753","answer":"148253697253769148679418235314675829826391574795824316431587962567932481982146753"},"85":{"question":"007020000004000009000000200213400007000000000708000564031500008042931670075084002","answer":"167829453324156789589347216213465897456798321798213564631572948842931675975684132"},"86":{"question":"900003070020007600000000104000300000340790200080005040030502007650004000892670003","answer":"916423578428157639573869124261348795345796281789215346134582967657934812892671453"},"87":{"question":"000001000000450000060230000000300098305008020009024315000800000700003064806972501","answer":"257681943913457682468239157124365798375198426689724315531846279792513864846972531"},"88":{"question":"000300008000008070008000036210030800075800002009020300500607904000900681000140053","answer":"127369548463518279958274136214736895375891462689425317531687924742953681896142753"},"89":{"question":"702000050000050000060000020000000007050009010897000000021094008600807902908602501","answer":"782146359419253786563978124136485297254769813897321465321594678645817932978632541"},"90":{"question":"000004000000000000609007120010060000405700003708100040001876490040930070076502030","answer":"127684359354219768689357124213465987465798213798123546531876492842931675976542831"},"91":{"question":"060870000004050080008009146020065897050000003000000000300007020040900571800021600","answer":"162874359934156782578239146421365897759418263683792415315647928246983571897521634"},"92":{"question":"000500020020409000089000000210350080000800000008004005701005090802000057900782413","answer":"163578924527419368489263571214356789395827146678194235731645892842931657956782413"},"93":{"question":"900870002020050009570120300015307000040090500000061000400002975000000000000700460","answer":"964873152123456789578129346215347698346298517789561234431682975657914823892735461"},"94":{"question":"000962001100000000000000200200070000000080007008614500431000950502091700900503002","answer":"375962481126458379849137265214375896653289147798614523431726958562891734987543612"},"95":{"question":"060000090020000000709000300200000009300090000800000103500040000008900732972683504","answer":"163257498425839671789164325254371869316498257897526143531742986648915732972683514"},"96":{"question":"000680000000007500009000000000000790005798000800000000001060904074901850930074621","answer":"152689347346217589789345162463152798215798436897436215521863974674921853938574621"},"97":{"question":"080007300000008070609020000200040800007200060096000034400792000758610920900800000","answer":"582467319134958672679123458215346897347289165896571234463792581758614923921835746"},"98":{"question":"000062000000000000070100200000400806450080300890600000031000068782000140004831002","answer":"145362789328579614679148235217493856456287391893615427531724968782956143964831572"},"99":{"question":"005009002020008609780006000000000000000800063096023401041007920560010000078002504","answer":"615379842423158679789246135137465298254891763896723451341587926562914387978632514"},"100":{"question":"940000000000000089060200100200005800006008000089024305005712900601980024000006031","answer":"947831652123567489568249173214375896356198247789624315435712968671983524892456731"},"101":{"question":"090024060100060009070009000000070000456801000789030405030047000840000000962580040","answer":"395124867124768359678359124213475698456891273789236415531647982847912536962583741"},"102":{"question":"008200010000000000009008000000306008000019024896004000000902870082573040900680300","answer":"348265917265197483719438265421356798537819624896724531153942876682573149974681352"},"103":{"question":"000060000020000080000000257204300800350091002000024000605012000040086023000540760","answer":"178265934523479186496138257264357819357891642819624375635712498741986523982543761"},"104":{"question":"000000100000000070700005040213006780000008600098710004000004920002001400904530060","answer":"325647198146389572789125346213456789457298613698713254531864927862971435974532861"},"105":{"question":"040100006000000000500000000000030098306009400807000000030065070075921803082703500","answer":"243178956719256384568394721451637298326589417897412635934865172675921843182743569"},"106":{"question":"000000040000100070000040030000060009007090203008072010300086504700023861986500020","answer":"123657948845139672679248135231465789467891253598372416312786594754923861986514327"},"107":{"question":"608003400200059070009068020103000000050000000000000000040785060060000850985624000","answer":"618273495234159678579468123123546789456897231897312546341785962762931854985624317"},"108":{"question":"000080000000040000709235140003000708050008600098702050000870000865020430004563000","answer":"142689573536147289789235146213456798457398612698712354321874965865921437974563821"},"109":{"question":"000025308000160409000000100000050007056709000000013500048000050500892704970000001","answer":"417925368835167429629348175293456817156789243784213596348671952561892734972534681"},"110":{"question":"000037000000059000409000030014000060350091000690800051030540086065913042000006000","answer":"526137498183459627479268135214375869358691274697824351731542986865913742942786513"},"111":{"question":"006000010000000000000109000204000090300800460600000135430602057702010600865900301","answer":"926475813143268579578139246214356798357891462689724135431682957792513684865947321"},"112":{"question":"000060500040230600008100000012000090006008102007600305020000960003926000900001703","answer":"239864517145237689678159234312475896456398172897612345521743968783926451964581723"},"113":{"question":"006000010000000000000034260300000807050390100080712340701000000800020630900500002","answer":"236859714194276583578134269312465897457398126689712345721643958845927631963581472"},"114":{"question":"070000806004600050000000030003060700400008000098000065320506908045912003000800500","answer":"172395846934681257586274139253469781461758392798123465327546918845912673619837524"},"115":{"question":"008000000000000000060000120200506789056000201800003600631702900000900000982000017","answer":"128367495345291876769485123213546789456879231897123654631752948574918362982634517"},"116":{"question":"000640000030000609060000000020460090400090300089010456310820000600070020072500041","answer":"297643185534281679861957234123465798456798312789312456315824967648179523972536841"},"117":{"question":"400005006000000479078000000003450708506800003890123000350000980000900300000501000","answer":"412795836635218479978364125123456798546879213897123564351642987264987351789531642"},"118":{"question":"938040000020000000007000020000450000050700200000003000000604000040875930075931640","answer":"938142567124567389567389124213456798456798213789213456391624875642875931875931642"},"119":{"question":"000080306000060480000040025000050790500000000097203564001804900780935000050000000","answer":"124589376375162489968347125213456798546798213897213564631824957782935641459671832"},"120":{"question":"860190034003400000000038060000006090300000420008004005000000802000000953900573641","answer":"865197234273465189149238567421356798357819426698724315536941872714682953982573641"},"121":{"question":"000090000000208079000007000200006700456780003790003560000604007000002650067800030","answer":"172395846345268179689417325213546798456789213798123564521634987834972651967851432"},"122":{"question":"000000001000000009009000034200405097000879003890010050030000900000980340000530602","answer":"324697581158243769679158234213465897546879123897312456435726918762981345981534672"},"123":{"question":"000900010000300080000008030003465097050709003090000060041027900000000042902030070","answer":"238946715415372689679158234123465897856719423794283561341627958567891342982534176"},"124":{"question":"000000000000000080500209100020006008007090301000371040041680972060903800800724003","answer":"619538427234167589578249136123456798457892361986371245341685972762913854895724613"},"125":{"question":"000005000230078000060000070100050000000700000897000045302047006648920700070061320","answer":"781295463234678519569134278123456897456789132897312645312547986648923751975861324"},"126":{"question":"050000003000000578089200100003406000040000200090710000302584690860000000974000000","answer":"451678923236149578789235146123456789547893261698712435312584697865927314974361852"},"127":{"question":"080000034003000080000008000210007008300000240000620000508040001600900000970863452","answer":"182576934753294186496318725219437568365189247847625319538742691624951873971863452"},"128":{"question":"060000400100406780008009036004000000005208000096000020001640978000900503000530040","answer":"269873451153426789478159236824365197715298364396714825531642978642987513987531642"},"129":{"question":"801900003000060000600000000020006000000000230098010506010094807007802904984001002","answer":"841925673235167489679348125123456798456789231798213546312594867567832914984671352"},"130":{"question":"000705902103000500000030100000000709357800000090000003031000805005971324040000600","answer":"468715932123469578579238146214356789357892461896147253731624895685971324942583617"},"131":{"question":"004020100023050700007000000000000690040200007000000300401802060600010873070605401","answer":"564728139123459786897163254215347698349286517786591342431872965652914873978635421"},"132":{"question":"560100000000000009000300020010400000007000010000000045020600981806930402940502673","answer":"562149738134728569789356124213465897457893216698217345325674981876931452941582673"},"133":{"question":"040120090003500007500000023000306709350000000008200056400800970800000000000641538","answer":"647123895123589467589467123214356789356798214798214356461835972835972641972641538"},"134":{"question":"000673000004000008670040030000000089050007203090012056340000000000080004082730500","answer":"128673945534129678679548132213456789456897213897312456341265897765981324982734561"},"135":{"question":"680020000020000000000000030000030700057000000806704350500940067041685903000270000","answer":"683127495425369178179458236214536789357892614896714352532941867741685923968273541"},"136":{"question":"000000020000100000600007104123000000400090317000003402310000090500036281900020500","answer":"741359628238164975659287134123475869465892317897613452312548796574936281986721543"},"137":{"question":"000000000120000709060300125010000090306000070000020000500800007007913852902000401","answer":"459271386123568749768394125214637598396185274875429613531842967647913852982756431"},"138":{"question":"000600070040000060600000000302065000050890213007100400520006040000014602964702500","answer":"235641879148279365679358124312465987456897213897123456521936748783514692964782531"},"139":{"question":"200000000130050080009300025300000800400700001090003000501600070083592610900810000","answer":"258476139134259786679381425312945867465728391897163542521634978783592614946817253"},"140":{"question":"070000001003006000080100340200300000000070000000061000401690000800714093907830400","answer":"572483961143926578689157342216348759354279186798561234431695827825714693967832415"},"141":{"question":"007040068000689000000007000003465780006090210708000006001070092000000071002014630","answer":"127543968345689127689127354213465789456798213798231546531876492964352871872914635"},"142":{"question":"000000500105060389609000020003070600050801070700020000000704930804006750060000800","answer":"238149567145267389679538124923475618456891273781623495512784936894316752367952841"},"143":{"question":"300000000000000000080020040003000600406001000008260100532014978800975402000002500","answer":"314586729275349816689127345123458697456791283798263154532614978861975432947832561"},"144":{"question":"000000030000050000000000008200005000050800700780604315531706000670012003900000167","answer":"125487639863259471497163258214375896356891724789624315531746982678912543942538167"},"145":{"question":"090002000000000160078000000000050000450807002700013500002084070807005021060720003","answer":"194362758325978164678541239213456897456897312789213546932184675847635921561729483"},"146":{"question":"809040000000000009000000008000000897000097100798014006001002000000903710907050063","answer":"829345671134678529576129438412536897653897142798214356341762985265983714987451263"},"147":{"question":"000040800040200070089000205000000090400009003700002406501603080007094612964020000","answer":"273945861145268379689137245312456798456789123798312456521673984837594612964821537"},"148":{"question":"310007065000000008000006003000000090000000382007060000501002840602980030970000250","answer":"314827965256139478789456123123548697465791382897263514531672849642985731978314256"},"149":{"question":"200010000000260509060409020000000790000897031000003400001730005000950007970680000","answer":"249315876137268549568479123813546792452897631796123458621734985384951267975682314"},"150":{"question":"900600020003008000000000005000000000007800000000000310031065982092003407086924001","answer":"914657823253418679678239145125346798347891256869572314431765982592183467786924531"},"151":{"question":"400020800000309000000000200010000679040000000000000054050704980862905703904002510","answer":"431526897285379461697481235518243679349657128726198354153764982862915743974832516"},"152":{"question":"036095478000000360009000005012400090000000200607023000001000000004000752973582001","answer":"136295478245178369789346125312457896458619237697823514521764983864931752973582641"},"153":{"question":"000000000000034009000150000010000000000708100897000400500043070678029041000871650","answer":"132987564765234819489156237316492785254768193897315426521643978678529341943871652"},"154":{"question":"500000000000000600070000020004006090306008040800000036001840907740915803080673000","answer":"563127489219384675478569321154236798396758142827491536631842957742915863985673214"},"155":{"question":"000600050000000600509000000004360708300709004000200500030872065080901002000000013","answer":"143698257728153649569427381214365798356789124897214536431872965685931472972546813"},"156":{"question":"000039000100057080570000020000006098000800000800000004020684907740013802000000301","answer":"268139475194257683573468129412376598937845216856921734321684957749513862685792341"},"157":{"question":"060293000020400709009070200000360000000010004806004010000002070000901500002507003","answer":"467293158128456739359178246241365897573819624896724315935682471784931562612547983"},"158":{"question":"000500060030060000500000100023000090056700010809002000082001045610004870047000621","answer":"291538467734169582568247139123856794456793218879412356382671945615924873947385621"},"159":{"question":"206091004000207080009340000002460708400000210000020450500008900008070000903000862","answer":"256891374134257689789346125312465798465789213897123456521638947648972531973514862"},"160":{"question":"500000040100489000400000020000000009307000006098070200731002090845016002060003051","answer":"576321948123489567489567123214635789357298416698174235731852694845916372962743851"},"161":{"question":"005060294020000000079000030000000000000000010008030000301027986560080001907004023","answer":"135768294426359178879142635213475869754896312698231457341527986562983741987614523"},"162":{"question":"709000000000450000008009007204300000000090420800620071000742908007903010002510703","answer":"719238564326457189458169237264371895173895426895624371631742958547983612982516743"},"163":{"question":"405008137100000000000030000004300000300800020069070000531082060702046510000513800","answer":"425698137173254689698137245814325796357869421269471358531782964782946513946513872"},"164":{"question":"000504001000060000060000200200000009406007020090000406320045090080001040940780002","answer":"832574961154269387769138254278456139416397825593812476321645798687921543945783612"},"165":{"question":"007040500100060409059100067000006790300200040600471200530000800000800002000710603","answer":"867943521123567489459128367214356798375289146698471235531692874746835912982714653"},"166":{"question":"001002600240000500000000003000040869057600001690003000000875900000960302900000080","answer":"381752694249316578765498123123547869857629431694183257432875916578961342916234785"},"167":{"question":"010000078000000269700036045000050096056089000007002003000500000004893001900021530","answer":"612945378345178269789236145123457896456389712897612453231564987574893621968721534"},"168":{"question":"000002450103050600056009000200030700000098104070200005002040000607900803081070500","answer":"798362451123457689456189237214536798365798124879214365532841976647925813981673542"},"169":{"question":"040080600000000009000009005003000896456000107709000300321500008597020000000070502","answer":"942785613135246789678139245213457896456398127789612354321564978597823461864971532"},"170":{"question":"000000000050120000009000120000050096060892300007010200512000983678000040000085060","answer":"123548679756129438849367125231754896465892317987613254512476983678931542394285761"},"171":{"question":"050000000100000000470000000010365090060780010800004060501642078700001530900000041","answer":"652137489189426357473958126217365894364789215895214763531642978746891532928573641"},"172":{"question":"005001040106000050000005000300006000007009200600720000000860004803914570974530680","answer":"235671849146298357789345126312456798457189263698723415521867934863914572974532681"},"173":{"question":"900000203000000009608000100210040690300008020709000310030020970502000031097000000","answer":"951467283423185769678392145215743698346918527789256314834521976562879431197634852"},"174":{"question":"000004000103000000070060000010600807050000000089001530030700940600003001807410653","answer":"265174389143598762978362415412635897356987124789241536531726948694853271827419653"},"175":{"question":"001960000000108000080000120020005900006000300790000402000094706050706091007021543","answer":"431962875275148639689357124123475968546289317798613452312594786854736291967821543"},"176":{"question":"000700000000000700067100204010000000306090040708210000000502070805070603072030015","answer":"123745869984326751567189234219654387356897142748213596431562978895471623672938415"},"177":{"question":"070320000003000000000000000010506709000090020800270150000082000740013805908000310","answer":"175328496423169578689457231214536789357891624896274153531682947742913865968745312"},"178":{"question":"010000940200000070000000100000000789057890302096700415040000607702930050000607030","answer":"518276943239148576674359128123465789457891362896723415341582697762934851985617234"},"179":{"question":"040090007030000080000006034023460008450819200600700400000504900000970050005002001","answer":"146398527532147689879256134923465718457819263618723495281534976364971852795682341"},"180":{"question":"000008000040000600600000030000056000450700120098000050503004971870020000960003002","answer":"132648597749235618685197234217356489456789123398412756523864971874921365961573842"},"181":{"question":"000001000000060009680000120000006790000709231008020005021070900045092607900804300","answer":"257931846413268579689457123132546798564789231798123465321675984845392617976814352"},"182":{"question":"000004000020008070500070024203000007050007000009000460371005980005982731002000000","answer":"137254698924168375568379124213496857456837219789521463371645982645982731892713546"},"183":{"question":"002000000000000500000000038003406007406807010008000400029000705041025080070930601","answer":"132568974984173562567249138213456897456897213798312456329681745641725389875934621"},"184":{"question":"000000800030000450000300000003000098007000003698720014021600970005007040904530000","answer":"142956837736182459589374126213465798457819263698723514321648975865297341974531682"},"185":{"question":"400090200000000000000005000000050008040009010000002350302804965865001437004000800","answer":"451397286236148579789265143127453698543689712698712354312874965865921437974536821"},"186":{"question":"000004502200150000000030040000060000000098013700000005012549070845070900067020050","answer":"173684592294157638658932147431265789526798413789413265312549876845376921967821354"},"187":{"question":"050700106000000070000050000210400700405000002000300065001600043000921800070003621","answer":"352784196146239578789156234213465789465897312897312465521678943634921857978543621"},"188":{"question":"010700000000006700000000040020005800050007003090002405342070958060940301900000004","answer":"216784539439156782578239146123465897654897213897312465342671958765948321981523674"},"189":{"question":"000000600034000000000008000123400009400800000000310465002501006560904821901000003","answer":"215743698834196257679258134123465789456879312798312465342581976567934821981627543"},"190":{"question":"700800050020000789400070036000000800070090402000724010000000970000000520982500640","answer":"713869254526143789498275136234651897175398462869724315651432978347986521982517643"},"191":{"question":"945003000123007080008000300000360000000090000000004506030806050060901020890500400","answer":"945183672123657984678429315214365798356798241789214536432876159567941823891532467"},"192":{"question":"000003040200100709079040030100000000000000010008010064302500670005007901900020053","answer":"581973246234156789679248135123465897456789312798312564312594678845637921967821453"},"193":{"question":"401290850230008000780000100100405708540800006000000010300000060000000000900032500","answer":"461293857235178649789546123123465798547819236698327415352781964816954372974632581"},"194":{"question":"060000000030009000700400100300007000050000007890600410000730806043080000908065340","answer":"162378954435219768789456123316547289254891637897623415521734896643982571978165342"},"195":{"question":"016207000200009008509008100100040000007000030090070405040605800000080001980000300","answer":"816237594234159768579468123123546987457891632698372415341625879765983241982714356"},"196":{"question":"000094070000000080479120056210600700050780004000201063000050000042000000905000020","answer":"368594172521367489479128356214635798653789214897241563136852947742916835985473621"},"197":{"question":"000060300000200009600347020300070000050001237008603001501000900007900503000084010","answer":"275169348134258679689347125312475896456891237798623451521736984847912563963584712"},"198":{"question":"000500640004060500500000020100600000006008000700203400300800075605900310000301800","answer":"213587649894162537567439128128645793436798251759213486341826975685974312972351864"},"199":{"question":"300008000050030780709000034000400000065870010090010065501600040000000000970540300","answer":"314758692256934781789126534123465879465879213897213465531682947642397158978541326"},"200":{"question":"040008000020007000000060000000030098300801040800720000031000070000940850985102060","answer":"143598627526317984798264135217436598369851742854729316431685279672943851985172463"},"201":{"question":"000000005020000009400000007000300000065708124897204050031806072000032500000001063","answer":"173429685628157439459683217214365798365798124897214356531846972786932541942571863"},"202":{"question":"000001002000008500050009036010300790000002000000107200000004900080915024000703605","answer":"349561872167238549258479136412356798673892451895147263531624987786915324924783615"},"203":{"question":"850630000004150680000000030000000098000090300008070006300080900045916020980003014","answer":"851639472234157689679248135123465798467892351598371246312584967745916823986723514"},"204":{"question":"806005000004000000079040000000050089057090000000000000040681957760004000901537600","answer":"816275394234169578579348126123456789457893261698712435342681957765924813981537642"},"205":{"question":"005040800100009007000050000003405000406708000000003405341000900070031000960874531","answer":"295147863134689257687352149823415796456798312719263485341526978578931624962874531"},"206":{"question":"400000000000000000000000000010006008300089040698010325701045902862971050000020807","answer":"423157689156398274987462531214536798375289146698714325731845962862971453549623817"},"207":{"question":"060004000000567400050020007000000000075008100080401523031000904740003052802005001","answer":"167834295923567418458129367214356789375298146689471523531682974746913852892745631"},"208":{"question":"009000000020000009070159000200405007006090300090200000351700000002980540080030020","answer":"139624875425378169678159234213465987546897312897213456351742698762981543984536721"},"209":{"question":"000000030030250600009360004203005006050800007708613245005000000800026000960500080","answer":"627148539134259678589367124213475896456892317798613245345781962871926453962534781"},"210":{"question":"012900000000000000009406003020500060450080000090200400230690800000072031900000256","answer":"312957648564138729789426513823549167456781392197263485231695874645872931978314256"},"211":{"question":"900500000130060000500109000200000000000000002089010450320641900640980020090023640","answer":"962574138134268579578139264213456897456897312789312456327641985641985723895723641"},"212":{"question":"090040000140006000008050230003005000056800000009012056500600040030904001900001002","answer":"392748615145236789678159234213465897456897123789312456521673948837924561964581372"},"213":{"question":"050001000100078000000000000200530000005000000090620010531700086008000043902803051","answer":"354291678126378495789456132217534869465189327893627514531742986678915243942863751"},"214":{"question":"961000500200000000008000000100000090450000213000312060000600000640901000007540621","answer":"961237584234895176578164932123456897456789213789312465315628749642971358897543621"},"215":{"question":"000700000000008009000000000123405000000001020789006400204500900001904082097010003","answer":"312749658475168239968253174123475896546891327789326415234587961651934782897612543"},"216":{"question":"000830000000200000600450000210000000006008031097000000021605804504902307078010652","answer":"142836579735291468689457123213549786456728931897163245321675894564982317978314652"},"217":{"question":"702008001000000600000100200003060000000000100897000046001046970500903800078501004","answer":"732658491145297638689134257213465789456789123897312546321846975564973812978521364"},"218":{"question":"005000000030000080000038000000065897406700003700310050501674038040591000060023000","answer":"185246379234957186679138425312465897456789213798312654521674938843591762967823541"},"219":{"question":"850000000123570000400020350000000090000801246090005000030406902040000680080012030","answer":"857364129123579468469128357214637895375891246698245713531486972742953681986712534"},"220":{"question":"078004000100000009006000000004000700300700010780100003030876940600000871897001600","answer":"978214356123567489456389127214635798365798214789142563531876942642953871897421635"},"221":{"question":"000900000000000000579020300000400097050200100000700205300090600760801900905642710","answer":"234968571618375429579124368123456897457289136896713245341597682762831954985642713"},"222":{"question":"207041056040000300600000120012000098400100000000003010520090063073000040000030000","answer":"237841956145269387689357124312475698498126735756983412521794863873612549964538271"},"223":{"question":"000910500000400709400300106200007000000100074000200005002840000800690000906705030","answer":"627918543138456729459372186264537918385169274791284365512843697873691452946725831"},"224":{"question":"000000301000400009070100050000005090056789100000000530000872005062031004087500203","answer":"245697381613458729879123456128345697356789142794216538431872965562931874987564213"},"225":{"question":"000000000003000450400103600000056007005009000790001360531400982000000030906030500","answer":"629584173183672459457193628814356297365729814792841365531467982248915736976238541"},"226":{"question":"070080000000409678009300004000000080000198200698704300030040000000003000040070830","answer":"174286593325419678869357124217635489453198267698724315731842956582963741946571832"},"227":{"question":"006001000000006000009000100014365807300089004000120000500042900042097531000503600","answer":"426951783183276459759438126214365897365789214897124365531642978642897531978513642"},"228":{"question":"000000006023000009000000000004060007300000000780014560031542070800931604005670320","answer":"147359286523486719968127435254863197316795842789214563631542978872931654495678321"},"229":{"question":"000090002000050000009000030000005007050700200706820050000002970805031004042680013","answer":"513496782287153469469278135124365897358719246796824351631542978875931624942687513"},"230":{"question":"000800050006000478000050100120000000005000007897061000500030704600904030904700000","answer":"219847356356129478748356129123478965465293817897561243581632794672984531934715682"},"231":{"question":"080010450000000700000070100010005007060700014708024065530000070072500600940000020","answer":"387216459124953786659478132413685297265739814798124365536842971872591643941367528"},"232":{"question":"040000000130000000000030005000400007007360100008712400500080000063970512070520800","answer":"245697381136845279789231645312458967457369128698712453524183796863974512971526834"},"233":{"question":"000002000000000009000008030210000090460080103007200040500604978006091050080030010","answer":"143962587852173469679458231218345796465789123397216845531624978726891354984537612"},"234":{"question":"090084060004060009000150230010405090000890000780000000000000006840916700067030001","answer":"192384567534267189678159234213475698456891372789623415321748956845916723967532841"},"235":{"question":"700000005023000080080000000215300607000701028890562000000075900000000070008023400","answer":"741289365623154789589637241215348697364791528897562134436875912952416873178923456"},"236":{"question":"600100000103008060089056000010030690000801402800000010001702000002900080970005240","answer":"645129837123478569789356124214537698356891472897264315431782956562943781978615243"},"237":{"question":"000000100003060500000030048010000000000097010609810300000051982052083060001024750","answer":"246578139183469527597132648718346295435297816629815374374651982952783461861924753"},"238":{"question":"000800000020000080508100000210000090057090040009210050030540920840900700000703400","answer":"164832579923475681578169234216354897357698142489217356731546928845921763692783415"},"239":{"question":"060000004120000008000100035200006009307091020096000153030000092040080000900002307","answer":"563278914124359678879164235215436789387591426496827153631745892742983561958612347"},"240":{"question":"008002000005100409070040020100000000006080000807000540350824067700900000080675312","answer":"418392675235167489679548123123456798546789231897213546351824967762931854984675312"},"241":{"question":"000000263000400000689000140200305007050091000000824001035002978800073000000040002","answer":"547189263123456789689237145214365897358791426796824351435612978862973514971548632"},"242":{"question":"070000001120400070680007000204060000006080000098000006531900480840570000907000000","answer":"473652891125498673689137245214369758356781924798245316531926487842573169967814532"},"243":{"question":"000094000230108000080350004023000000050809307090010000341000000000002001060040783","answer":"517294638234168579689357124123475896456829317798613245341786952875932461962541783"},"244":{"question":"010070000200100000000200008020400097056890003000300400000001006760003520980500730","answer":"518679342234158679679234158123465897456897213897312465345721986761983524982546731"},"245":{"question":"009000000003457000000009040210005098050800000890020000031506000005942003980100064","answer":"149238657623457981578619342214365798357891426896724135431586279765942813982173564"},"246":{"question":"075000004000000080000100005003005800050000300000200056031624008802001040040030620","answer":"175382964324596187698147235213465879456879312987213456731624598862951743549738621"},"247":{"question":"000000810003000000000100034000070000050001020807246000001080790762034581905010002","answer":"249763815513428679678159234124375968356891427897246153431582796762934581985617342"},"248":{"question":"000080206000060080000000000000006000006008025800205003480601052001950874950870601","answer":"139587246245169387678423519523716498796348125814295763487631952361952874952874631"},"249":{"question":"000020000000009078079068100210030080000091000000200305000080057762000030905013000","answer":"148327596326159478579468123217534689653891742894276315431682957762945831985713264"},"250":{"question":"005020090000000070409037250200000709006098000007000503030000007600970010008005600","answer":"175426398823519476469837251284351769356798124917264583531682947642973815798145632"},"251":{"question":"400000950005040070000000000000000789540100063000720000300010897860937001970502300","answer":"426371958135849672789256134213465789547198263698723415352614897864937521971582346"},"252":{"question":"000000001100200070070000058310065800060090120807310460020703000000900000086500000","answer":"245678931138259674679134258312465897564897123897312465921743586453986712786521349"},"253":{"question":"000008000005000000080005000000400008406380020897000405001793000008020073070864510","answer":"124938756735146892689275341213457968456389127897612435561793284948521673372864519"},"254":{"question":"090080000000450080500300004200000000007108006000704300001045962800903001905012073","answer":"194286537326457189578391624213569748457138296689724315731845962862973451945612873"},"255":{"question":"456870000000000678000000045210000000060708000807000056000040000602900507970021403","answer":"456872139123495678789136245215369784364758921897214356531647892642983517978521463"},"256":{"question":"040035000000000000008009105003000708456008010700310006010500900504970800807020054","answer":"241835679935167482678249135123456798456798213789312546312584967564973821897621354"},"257":{"question":"008509000000000080000008060010306790000090000890000310001082070600973850000140000","answer":"128569437356417289479238165214356798763891542895724316531682974642973851987145623"},"258":{"question":"002060007000000009008000000103006700450091006000000400031085070590700860080000350","answer":"312469587645378129978152643123546798457891236869237415231685974594713862786924351"},"259":{"question":"000080000005040700608000005000450090006008000009600004001500900507823001860900502","answer":"124785639935146728678239145782451396416398257359672814241567983597823461863914572"},"260":{"question":"000042000020000000008100000014035090005807100090204005001000907006983500002001003","answer":"139542876527368419648179352714635298265897134893214765351426987476983521982751643"},"261":{"question":"090000000030007000000009005000065000000891000869300450321580070700013800900720513","answer":"192658347538147269647239185213465798475891632869372451321584976756913824984726513"},"262":{"question":"801000000200030608000000035000406700056090000700010000312580007007021803900760001","answer":"831675294245139678679248135123456789456897312798312456312584967567921843984763521"},"263":{"question":"008041000000500000000000000000306097005092600009074320031000086000600500846005002","answer":"658941273213587469794263851482356197375192648169874325531429786927618534846735912"},"264":{"question":"060000902000469070000000040205000000306000000098025000031000007057980401982004653","answer":"164578932523469178879231546215346789346897215798125364431652897657983421982714653"},"265":{"question":"090000000000300000000000030000005006000010007080900400701540060800796513065830742","answer":"193254678246387195578169234312475986459618327687923451731542869824796513965831742"},"266":{"question":"640020000030000000000406000000540080406000000897603000010700006074960032068005014","answer":"641328579235197468789456123123549687456872391897613245312784956574961832968235714"},"267":{"question":"087000000000400000400000000000060000005800000790020000031640070072930410049501632","answer":"187253946923486157456197283214765398365819724798324561531642879672938415849571632"},"268":{"question":"000030060020000000400109030214300000300008000780912000002790041805020000071840000","answer":"597234168123586479468179532214357986359468217786912354632795841845621793971843625"},"269":{"question":"040000203023056000600000000200360000358001020000000351030600070802970014001048002","answer":"547189263123456789689237145214365897358791426796824351435612978862973514971548632"},"270":{"question":"050742000100000000470000050000000089060090020800210360500000690700900830901000502","answer":"653742918128359476479168253214536789365897124897214365532481697746925831981673542"},"271":{"question":"009007050000108079578000123020500800050090030006203504040002005000900000002030001","answer":"169327458234158679578469123321546897457891236896273514643712985715984362982635741"},"272":{"question":"200000000030006780000009000010000007400090000700002400621500900073920045000670310","answer":"246187539139256784587349126312465897468793251795812463621534978873921645954678312"},"273":{"question":"000040297000009000009050000000465700000090000698703400301087052070900603900000801","answer":"513846297264179538789352164132465789457298316698713425341687952875921643926534871"},"274":{"question":"005000001046030070080000030300060009450000000090702300520903067064007003003600452","answer":"235874691146239578789156234312465789457398126698712345521943867864527913973681452"},"275":{"question":"380090150025007000000050000000060000050700300000200000000824976840930021900001800","answer":"384692157125347689679158234213465798456789312798213465531824976847936521962571843"},"276":{"question":"006800000000000600780040135103405008050000010600710054300000000060970000001504803","answer":"236851479514397682789642135193465728457238916628719354342186597865973241971524863"},"277":{"question":"700100050000050000400000006004500008070000405895004207507000000041280003980763500","answer":"723146859168952374459378126214537968376829415895614237537491682641285793982763541"},"278":{"question":"700940516020000000000170000000060000000000100000003065341607950070890340082004071","answer":"738942516124356789569178234213465897456789123897213465341627958675891342982534671"},"279":{"question":"000000302000000008080036005003050009047090000690312400000004026070900004904503781","answer":"165789342732145698489236175213457869547698213698312457351874926876921534924563781"},"280":{"question":"001080290000009070009005000000400000007008600008010040012064957060970000074023801","answer":"431687295256139478789245136123456789547398612698712543312864957865971324974523861"},"281":{"question":"000605000005000609670009040010450000000098000000203000001862900700904560900001830","answer":"129645387345187629678329145213456798456798213897213456531862974782934561964571832"},"282":{"question":"050078103000000000080000000003400000065080012807000405006501978570800000900600031","answer":"652978143134256789789134256213465897465789312897312465326541978571893624948627531"},"283":{"question":"000031000103000079000009100000000000000097001080020000001082960670910400892700003","answer":"729431658143658279568279134917345826256897341384126795431582967675913482892764513"},"284":{"question":"507600000000009600400000005004005009000800100090004000630042000070901462042700003","answer":"517623894328459671469178235184365729253897146796214358631542987875931462942786513"},"285":{"question":"000001000120079400009040000200050089000800213000100000530082000700930051980615300","answer":"345261798128379465679548132213457689457896213896123574531782946762934851984615327"},"286":{"question":"000000020005008600070000148123050000000089200708010400000004080560070030900020700","answer":"841697325235148679679235148123456897456789213798312456317964582562871934984523761"},"287":{"question":"600090010000000089009100007000056790050709020708013000301900000000030900975608030","answer":"632897514147365289589142367213456798456789123798213645321974856864531972975628431"},"288":{"question":"000000030200040070600200045020456807000807312009000406000000080017900063900003720","answer":"145678239293145678678239145321456897456897312789312456532761984817924563964583721"},"289":{"question":"000503001000060508500007040005000080000098025000010003000602010650074002902031600","answer":"467583291123469578589127346215346789346798125798215463834652917651974832972831654"},"290":{"question":"006008000000400008089106000000000080000000064698000050030502806800000007975600410","answer":"246358179153497628789126345324765981517839264698214753431572896862941537975683412"},"291":{"question":"000000000300006709080000020000400078450000000798003500010804960864002001930010802","answer":"271598436345126789689347125123459678456781293798263514512834967864972351937615842"},"292":{"question":"000800000100000008780000240004365089050298060090700350030072806002000000075600400","answer":"543826917129457638786139245214365789357298164698714352431572896862941573975683421"},"293":{"question":"006000800000068470070039050014006000000800010009000300002000940000973582890405601","answer":"136547829925168473478239156214356798763894215589712364352681947641973582897425631"},"294":{"question":"500000100020000008068000009004056007306807204709000050000702905840000700975031000","answer":"593248176127569438468173529214956387356817294789324651631782945842695713975431862"},"295":{"question":"000090000000050000000007000204000900005000247090620350031000090872940000900530782","answer":"123498576687153429459267813214375968365819247798624351531782694872946135946531782"},"296":{"question":"000000000103050600060000000000000080000000042890010065631502000042986513005700006","answer":"478369251123457698569128734254693187316875942897214365631542879742986513985731426"},"297":{"question":"000070054000136009600000120000507096400200017000300000000004978702000431000003560","answer":"138972654245136789679458123321547896456289317897361245513624978762895431984713562"},"298":{"question":"000200007030060009078000000000456008400000200000020000300678952082010000700530841","answer":"149285367235167489678349125921456738457893216863721594314678952582914673796532841"},"299":{"question":"000040005240060070609000020000400000406890000097000051031080040062004893980706000","answer":"173249685248561379659378124325417968416895237897623451531982746762154893984736512"}},"hard":{"0":{"question":"000041008000060070000000030000000800005002004000000025000704900706000501892100043","answer":"367941258128563479459278136214635897675892314983417625531784962746329581892156743"},"1":{"question":"500100000000000560700050023210500600000000030097300015020000000005000000908025000","answer":"532146789189237564746859123213574698654918237897362415421783956365491872978625341"},"2":{"question":"002000600345000200000200030003000800000089000000000300000506080568090400004003061","answer":"172438659345961278689275134913752846426389715857614392231546987568197423794823561"},"3":{"question":"908000000020000670060000008200000806000006201000000000000000900090582013000013765","answer":"918267354324158679567349128231795846475836291689421537153674982796582413842913765"},"4":{"question":"000218600003050080008000120000030806006000050800000300000040000600083500907005040","answer":"459218637123657489768394125214539876376821954895476312531942768642783591987165243"},"5":{"question":"000060000230000000070000000120400000006800003089000001300010000561004732092730000","answer":"914263578238547169675198324123459687756821943489376251347612895561984732892735416"},"6":{"question":"051800000000100000008050000003000000005000710700000005010084000000926801090001400","answer":"251837649349162578678459123163795284985243716724618395512384967437926851896571432"},"7":{"question":"000002007006040500780000004023000090507200003000003000300000000060000902005028400","answer":"154392687236847519789156324423561798597284163618973245342719856861435972975628431"},"8":{"question":"000000000100306700000078130000000890050090026000020410040000008005030001070500603","answer":"387142569129356784564978132412763895758491326936825417643217958895634271271589643"},"9":{"question":"050000000000000009600034050020000800000000300090312400000506980006000020907021536","answer":"152689743834275619679134258325467891461958372798312465213546987586793124947821536"},"10":{"question":"004003000030089000780406000010500009065008001000002000000704000000000000043000710","answer":"154273698236189457789456123312547869465398271897612345521734986678921534943865712"},"11":{"question":"600000000024000600089067000003040807006780001090203050000670002000000010000020000","answer":"635492178724138695189567243513946827246785931897213456451679382362854719978321564"},"12":{"question":"000300000003000009000000000000005008050807104709000000530000002067002503940050601","answer":"125349867473568219698271435214635798356897124789124356531486972867912543942753681"},"13":{"question":"500608374000007000700040000003400700400000603000010000030060000000000432970002001","answer":"512698374346127589789345126123456798457289613698713245231864957865971432974532861"},"14":{"question":"000000020000300080000000305003060000400001000095200400500082004086010032040000871","answer":"314578629259346187678129345123465798467891253895237416531782964786914532942653871"},"15":{"question":"000000400000050000089000000000465000065000000000012006321578004500001800070604300","answer":"152386479437159268689247153713465982265893741894712536321578694546931827978624315"},"16":{"question":"000000500000000000000000004123000007450000013000213460002000008075030940900607350","answer":"214376589368459721597821634123564897456798213789213465632945178875132946941687352"},"17":{"question":"700000050000400670000300104000000080000100006008200300000005800000943501965000032","answer":"714862953239451678586397124421536789357189246698274315143625897872943561965718432"},"18":{"question":"000000000000407500050108000000000708305000004097200000030000070002901853008600041","answer":"123596487689437512754128369246315798315789624897264135531842976462971853978653241"},"19":{"question":"000000010005200009070009040003400008006008127000600053000000964004020070001004000","answer":"239547816145286739678139245513472698496358127782691453327815964864923571951764382"},"20":{"question":"008000000030060070000000000000050009006807012800010405020080000783920050040601000","answer":"158472693439568271267193548314256789596847312872319465621785934783924156945631827"},"21":{"question":"001002000204000000000000003023500090000000000008000040012805070007924030005001060","answer":"531472689264389157879156423123547896746298315958613742312865974687924531495731268"},"22":{"question":"000000010000000000000000000000060098400800006600000145501970860040502000970030001","answer":"253786914164293587789145623325461798417859236698327145531974862846512379972638451"},"23":{"question":"000005670005000200600009000002050007456000010000310450500000904000000000900000003","answer":"123485679795136248648279135312654897456798312879312456531827964267943581984561723"},"24":{"question":"000090000000007489070000030000000000000000006090000000020904800063580042980670010","answer":"138496275256317489479258631312865794847129356695743128521934867763581942984672513"},"25":{"question":"030000005020000000000000006000000000007009063600000020300502678802630900965071002","answer":"134267895526918347789345216413726589257489163698153724341592678872634951965871432"},"26":{"question":"010030000230100000600000000000400009006090000098002305040506092875900003900003000","answer":"514238976237169584689754231153487629426395718798612345341576892875921463962843157"},"27":{"question":"009800010000000670000040000010000090400000003800002000001003080004900300080524761","answer":"239867415145239678678145239312456897456798123897312546521673984764981352983524761"},"28":{"question":"000900050000040009600020000000050090000009000000000460001002980560001030087034510","answer":"124963857375148629698725143713456298846219375259387461431572986562891734987634512"},"29":{"question":"000070000000000780070200000203400090050000203000000540302600000000002074000534621","answer":"124875936536149782879263415263458197458791263791326548342617859615982374987534621"},"30":{"question":"000120000000000000000000100004008607300000048700000000000042970602910034809073010","answer":"435126789281397465967584123154238697396751248728469351513842976672915834849673512"},"31":{"question":"000000030000008000000050100300400000006000000000003056500786900801932005000500002","answer":"124679538657318249983254167395467821416825793278193456532786914841932675769541382"},"32":{"question":"000030000034000500600000020000000080000000230000000000000384607786010304900670812","answer":"125436978834297561679158423261543789497861235358729146512384697786912354943675812"},"33":{"question":"000000004000006089570100000003060097007891060000003000030500000042010000080600001","answer":"168329574324756189579148632213465897457891263896273415731582946642917358985634721"},"34":{"question":"006001000020400080000200067200000000365700014090000000001600002000005001000010605","answer":"436871259527469183189253467214596378365728914798134526951647832642385791873912645"},"35":{"question":"000200070006107089080000000003009000000602001090301245002004010000000000000715032","answer":"134298576526137489789456123213549768845672391697381245352964817971823654468715932"},"36":{"question":"800003000003000789060008100004300090000009002090020000000002608000001000080000041","answer":"812793564453216789769458123124365897638179452597824316971542638346981275285637941"},"37":{"question":"007105620000000580000208000003400008000010060000820000000080006070030851000600300","answer":"387145629124369587569278134753496218842517963691823745235781496476932851918654372"},"38":{"question":"000005000000060500570008000120000000456800000090010065000600000000001002907532801","answer":"612345789389167524574298316123756498456829173798413265231684957845971632967532841"},"39":{"question":"034600000156000000700005200312000700000000003000000060521860000043001800000023600","answer":"234617589156289374789345216312456798465798123897132465521864937643971852978523641"},"40":{"question":"060003000023000000580107000000370809000298100098000005000000002000906000000030086","answer":"164523798723489651589167243416375829357298164298614375675841932832956417941732586"},"41":{"question":"000603070006070000009045006023400080465008000800000460502000000000000000000500000","answer":"148623579256179348379845126723416985465298713891357462512964837934782651687531294"},"42":{"question":"900000000024300009060000000010000007050007000000000000341702905072000081090030740","answer":"935124678724368159168975234213456897659817423487293516341782965572649381896531742"},"43":{"question":"004200000000000408700040030010000700400001000098000004601000040000017090975600002","answer":"154238679263179458789546231316492785427851963598763124631925847842317596975684312"},"44":{"question":"000070000020400000678059124000000098300090000000010003001000000007001040800040650","answer":"435172869129468735678359124714623598382795416956814273241536987567981342893247651"},"45":{"question":"706804000000000000480000007204350000000700000000240000002008076000900850978005014","answer":"716824395325197468489563127264351789153789642897246531532418976641972853978635214"},"46":{"question":"000000000200030009000007000020065000456008000000002006300680900060901308000023600","answer":"134259867275836419689147235821365794456798123793412586317684952562971348948523671"},"47":{"question":"000000500100070060500000000000000000000000000897000050030754000702010645945286000","answer":"364128579128975364579463128213547896456891237897632451631754982782319645945286713"},"48":{"question":"000008107045037000000040200002050000400000090600370400000000000003904006000700010","answer":"236598147145237689789146235312459768457681392698372451521863974873914526964725813"},"49":{"question":"000870000120000009600100205004000000050090120090000000001027008060000000080543001","answer":"549872316123456789678139245214365897356798124897214563431627958765981432982543671"},"50":{"question":"000102058000300600000079003010540000000000000080000000040700060070001380000630010","answer":"394162758721385649568479123217543896439816275685927431143798562976251384852634917"},"51":{"question":"500080000020000000000200000210065000050790003098003450001576002060000000070000561","answer":"534681279127349685689257314213465798456798123798123456841576932365912847972834561"},"52":{"question":"000000005000000300008070100000050000400890003700003050370000902002980037800002041","answer":"123648795547129368968375124231456879456897213789213456374561982612984537895732641"},"53":{"question":"000508010040000000078100000300400000000091000007360001520600073000905100904010060","answer":"239548617145276389678139524312457896456891732897362451521684973763925148984713265"},"54":{"question":"350207000000360009000400020000506098000000005000023000001000000040905002000100600","answer":"354297186127368549689451327213546798468719235975823461531682974746935812892174653"},"55":{"question":"300004060020006080009000034000400890000080100000013400000500000042097000070030602","answer":"358924761421376589769158234217465893534289176896713425683542917142697358975831642"},"56":{"question":"000004100000200500000030040000056790000008002000300005000000820600070000847900651","answer":"235684179469217583178539246324156798591748362786392415913465827652871934847923651"},"57":{"question":"000200000020000000470030000000005890300009000000024000001000070700900000902573604","answer":"135296487628457931479138256214765893356819742897324165541682379763941528982573614"},"58":{"question":"040000000000450680000009045000000790006790000000010000000800050000900870897532060","answer":"145286937729453681368179245451328796286794513973615428612847359534961872897532164"},"59":{"question":"072003000000050000060008003000500000056000017700002000000800974080024000000700802","answer":"172463589348957126569218743213576498856349217794182635621835974987624351435791862"},"60":{"question":"800000001020306000570100000200400800050090300000000104000002005000000000002570613","answer":"834257961129346578576189432217435896458691327693728154341962785765813249982574613"},"61":{"question":"000000048300020000000000003000040090400801000000070000000000981700985302900002700","answer":"125397648346128579879456123261543897497861235538279416652734981714985362983612754"},"62":{"question":"260100003005008000009000000300460090000009000698020000500000080000970002900082001","answer":"264195873135748269789236145352461798417859326698327514523614987841973652976582431"},"63":{"question":"000004000000068070000000004200070800400000000000020105001006902806002701070500060","answer":"127354689594168273638297514213475896465819327789623145341786952856942731972531468"},"64":{"question":"000000000000060500569000100000006709007001200800720005000080007070003801080007423","answer":"123458976748169532569372148214536789357891264896724315431285697672943851985617423"},"65":{"question":"704000050000000000000060004200300000040000000890100040030000587000514000050800401","answer":"714238659326495178589761234267349815145687392893152746431926587678514923952873461"},"66":{"question":"000200000023070000000000125000005090065000000080100000001080900040051080897020051","answer":"456218379123579468978346125214735896365894217789162534531687942642951783897423651"},"67":{"question":"000300052003000000000279106000030000000890200700020005501486000000002000800000001","answer":"167348952293165478458279136612537849345891267789624315521486793936712584874953621"},"68":{"question":"800002000000006000000070100003000600000000007708010005341005906600034800005700402","answer":"814352769237196584569478123123547698456289317798613245341825976672934851985761432"},"69":{"question":"000500900100000008000000006000050080007890000690070000001700090000010820982605410","answer":"234568971156927348879341256413256789527893164698174532341782695765419823982635417"},"70":{"question":"006000400000007009570000003003000700000000006089013050041000060705001000892070500","answer":"916238475234157689578469123123546798457892316689713254341925867765381942892674531"},"71":{"question":"006030000103050700000109000000000007000090100000010000030602000640980205890503001","answer":"926738514183254769475169382314826957258397146769415823531672498647981235892543671"},"72":{"question":"900000008000000000600000000000000000000000283700600415002000047014000062800942500","answer":"921354678435768129678219354243581796156497283789623415592136847314875962867942531"},"73":{"question":"080000076100400000007080004200006790300700025000020001000000000702000800856003012","answer":"584139276123467589967285134215346798348791625679528341431852967792614853856973412"},"74":{"question":"010000050000008600000000004100400890000000210000000000231000006004090002070032501","answer":"312649758457218639698357124163425897849763215725981463231574986584196372976832541"},"75":{"question":"009028000100000000070009000210000800006000020090000000000002970042981050005073402","answer":"369128547124735689578469231217356894456897123893214765631542978742981356985673412"},"76":{"question":"000000300000047009000008100123005006000280000000000000002000068004021000957836240","answer":"461592387238147659579368124123475896746289513895613472312754968684921735957836241"},"77":{"question":"508000010000000070070000060000350097306080020000000005602000001085690040001000750","answer":"528467319163925478479138562214356897356789124897214635642573981785691243931842756"},"78":{"question":"000000240000000070000200008200065007000001006600000015000006002702580961006102030","answer":"137658249528419673469237158214865397875391426693724815351946782742583961986172534"},"79":{"question":"000830400000160009070059103003006000005090000700010005000000074090000000040000006","answer":"159832467234167589678459123913526748425798631786314295361285974597643812842971356"},"80":{"question":"500069004100000080000008007000000800000801402000620000000002000701080023900540700","answer":"528769134137254689469318257213495876675831492894627315356172948741986523982543761"},"81":{"question":"490201600100460009678000000000030008006790000700000300030000900002070010040005030","answer":"495281673123467589678359124214536798356798241789124356531842967862973415947615832"},"82":{"question":"070000030030060079000040125002050700000000010700000500020000080007000300040002600","answer":"174295836235168479689347125312856794456973218798421563521634987867519342943782651"},"83":{"question":"207000090130000500009000000302040709000708230700000605500004000040900002970600000","answer":"257136498134289567689457123362541789495768231718392645523814976846975312971623854"},"84":{"question":"000000800000000000000100030000000060006800307000200050001502006002091500905603100","answer":"123456879457938612869127435514379268296815347738264951381542796642791583975683124"},"85":{"question":"005090208000000509000200030013000096000000020090023400300080052000900700000030640","answer":"135496278427318569689275134213754896854169327796823415341687952562941783978532641"},"86":{"question":"000000000000060080400000000204000008000009010090471230501002906006050800000006543","answer":"162398457379564182485127369214635798753289614698471235531842976946753821827916543"},"87":{"question":"000000000030050000000400100300546080450000236690000005700000090001005007000000002","answer":"124367958839152674576489123312546789457891236698273415743628591261935847985714362"},"88":{"question":"500000000000000000009006040000000007000009000600700053320600900861900532970500801","answer":"512493786436857129789126345143285697257369418698741253325618974861974532974532861"},"89":{"question":"704800091000400070000027040200000000040000000097000000030500960000904013908030500","answer":"724853691153469278689127345215346789346798152897215436431582967562974813978631524"},"90":{"question":"000020000000000000080047000003006790000700200000010006300600900002504300974030650","answer":"135928467427165839689347125213456798546789213798213546351672984862594371974831652"},"91":{"question":"006000000020000070000008000000000789000000402698000153000000000005000024902670300","answer":"136257948824139576759468231243516789517893462698742153461325897375981624982674315"},"92":{"question":"000060500100000600000000007012400096006190200009023015000734000070010300900000001","answer":"237861549145279683698345127312457896756198234489623715521734968874916352963582471"},"93":{"question":"080001000003000000000000060010300008005009010007104300538000004601000025902045030","answer":"286531749193467582754298163419376258365829417827154396538912674641783925972645831"},"94":{"question":"000000900100000000609100000000460789000000003000000450520070690000020370976000000","answer":"234586917157293846689147532312465789495718263768932451523871694841629375976354128"},"95":{"question":"090000005020000000000009204200307000000000010709001000000005900608070021070600800","answer":"193246785425738169867159234214367598586492317739581642341825976658973421972614853"},"96":{"question":"900000000030100089608300005020005800000000000000210056000000000040900301000631500","answer":"912458637435167289678329145126745893753896412894213756361574928547982361289631574"},"97":{"question":"000000000104307080600000000000405008000708000000003546000070960042000851006014000","answer":"235681479194357682678249135361425798459768213827193546513872964742936851986514327"},"98":{"question":"001600800050000200000030050000456790005000000897002005502003074000000080000500620","answer":"231675849456189237789234156123456798645798312897312465512863974364927581978541623"},"99":{"question":"001000050000080000009000020100050780047000200000070005000760004800000002904532871","answer":"381426957726985143459317628132654789547891236698273415213768594875149362964532871"},"100":{"question":"080060000020000680009000000203000090000200000000000400000024000002501000940036521","answer":"184362759325179684679458213213645897496287135857913462531824976762591348948736521"},"101":{"question":"900000640100000009450000020000600790000700200008004350000000900002901835009200060","answer":"923517648186342579457869123231658794564793281798124356375486912642971835819235467"},"102":{"question":"000208004020000000008060200010000000000090000009020300501002900007900500090010043","answer":"135278694426139758978564231213657489754893126869421375541382967387946512692715843"},"103":{"question":"940000008000008400070000000100000090000090031000200040002004960004030002000620314","answer":"941352678236178459578469123123546897465897231789213546312784965654931782897625314"},"104":{"question":"000600000040100260000000005000006000400090000700012450002860000860073020900520040","answer":"125637894348159267697248315251486739436795182789312456512864973864973521973521648"},"105":{"question":"830100070020070000070000004000000009407001300698703000300580000000000003005037240","answer":"834125976126479835579368124213846759457291368698753412341582697762914583985637241"},"106":{"question":"000105007000007000560489023000046008056000000000000000001850070600000000900000050","answer":"234165897189237465567489123712546938456398712893712546321854679645973281978621354"},"107":{"question":"000080000000300000000000030003070869400801000090600400040008900860032741001000203","answer":"134285697587369124629147538213574869456891372798623415342718956865932741971456283"},"108":{"question":"700004000200008000000200004003000960000800327800620415000900700600700500900006000","answer":"715364289246598173389217654423175968561849327897623415158932746634781592972456831"},"109":{"question":"000000000000007000450038000200000008000790005000800010000602974042970000976140020","answer":"123469587689517432457238169214356798368791245795824316531682974842973651976145823"},"110":{"question":"910000000030000070000009000000040000000800001700200000301782965672900004005000702","answer":"914327586236158479587469123128546397469873251753291648341782965672915834895634712"},"111":{"question":"000000003003450609000000008000000000000780100090005000000060982050902760960070530","answer":"145698273283457619679123458516349827324786195798215346437561982851932764962874531"},"112":{"question":"600040090000000000000000000100065000050098000800010050012500060500070021970000345","answer":"621347598345981276789652134134265789256798413897413652412539867563874921978126345"},"113":{"question":"001705000200000060000000000000007080000008300800013004318002040000004008004801532","answer":"461725893235189467789346125123457689546298371897613254318572946652934718974861532"},"114":{"question":"000000008100008000008000000010000800000000006080020305500647080040985631096002050","answer":"253164798164798523978253164319576842425831976687429315531647289742985631896312457"},"115":{"question":"000000000000050700008009000013000090400090062890703410002510070780000000941000003","answer":"124376589369158724578249136213465897457891362896723415632514978785932641941687253"},"116":{"question":"501009008000030500700400020100007000000001007000000000012005004804000000070820301","answer":"521679438468132579739458126143287695685391247297546813312765984854913762976824351"},"117":{"question":"000000000000000000000009000000000008005090000789124000031806002040003050008052031","answer":"123465789497381625856279314264537198315698247789124563531846972942713856678952431"},"118":{"question":"900000170020000089500100000000300090007090410009004050005000900000083500091000700","answer":"943268175126457389578139246452316897637895412819724653285671934764983521391542768"},"119":{"question":"007000000000000000600037000002400708000090002005380104021004030000006007976500480","answer":"137658249258149673649237815312465798864791352795382164521874936483916527976523481"},"120":{"question":"010000000200000000000060000000056700000800000008000010000080090700040050985612347","answer":"314275689256198473879364125192456738537821964468739512643587291721943856985612347"},"121":{"question":"000010000040000000000007000300000000450000238000000500000900846803020051960085002","answer":"235416789147398625689257413398542167451769238726831594512973846873624951964185372"},"122":{"question":"080301000000000000000080000302000090456700000090003000601000005000910000940075012","answer":"284351679137269584569487123312546798456798231798123456671832945825914367943675812"},"123":{"question":"000020800000000079050070200000035000060000000000001060500000940802950000906000083","answer":"173429856284563179659178234421635798365897421798241365517386942832954617946712583"},"124":{"question":"000000210000350009008000300000005000000090700700030154030600000840003000900007001","answer":"354769218172358469698124375413875692265491783789236154531682947847913526926547831"},"125":{"question":"300040000100000008009000000003006009007800023090000450000080030000012560904073012","answer":"325748691176259348489361275513426789647895123892137456251684937738912564964573812"},"126":{"question":"000000900020450000089007000004000060000000400897000051000000000560090030071020580","answer":"135268947726459318489137625214975863653812479897346251342581796568794132971623584"},"127":{"question":"005060000000000009070000000200000000000080007798604013501042968800506700900000004","answer":"145369872682175349379428156216937485453281697798654213531742968824596731967813524"},"128":{"question":"030010000000600009000349005200050007000000000800003450000700080702000501980001060","answer":"439215678125678349678349125213456897546897213897123456351762984762984531984531762"},"129":{"question":"200005000000008079670039000000056800000000003000020000000073004030902516000500030","answer":"219745368345168279678239145193456827762891453854327691521673984437982516986514732"},"130":{"question":"000310600000000080068009100000000000300000007089000010000000908095002403872040000","answer":"247318659913256784568479132124537896356891247789624315431765928695182473872943561"},"131":{"question":"000000000000000500600000000000470000000000002790600415305002046000900750007001823","answer":"134856297278319564659247138521473689486195372793628415315782946862934751947561823"},"132":{"question":"000000000100079060000108000000400000056800120000013400600000090000961042900500600","answer":"237645819184379265569128734312456978456897123798213456623784591875961342941532687"},"133":{"question":"000000200004000700000009030003000000000000312008003400001002900805010623902600571","answer":"136457289294381756587269134423195867759846312618723495361572948875914623942638571"},"134":{"question":"000070000000000479608000020100400000000890030700200500000000080007080000890031654","answer":"914372865235168479678549123123456798456897231789213546341625987567984312892731654"},"135":{"question":"900000400000000070400000000204056000000000000009010050000000000640082735802730600","answer":"913527468526148379478693521234856197165279843789314256357461982641982735892735614"},"136":{"question":"000000000100000009000089200214035090005000600000000300530000902000900001000002543","answer":"629347158178526439453189276214635897395278614786491325531764982842953761967812543"},"137":{"question":"004900008000060000009000124010030090040000010000020000000006000502801703070243600","answer":"724915368138462975659378124216534897347689512985127436493756281562891743871243659"},"138":{"question":"001000800000078000080000000000000000000890003090320010302704905870000000904580070","answer":"231459867456178239789236154123645798647891523598327416312764985875913642964582371"},"139":{"question":"000000000004000000000106000000000008006700020800213050531670900000594000002030000","answer":"123457896674389512985126473217965348356748129849213657531672984768594231492831765"},"140":{"question":"008000000000000000050000008000350000007001000009020300600080905040010602002564701","answer":"128436579496875213753192468264358197537941826819627354671283945345719682982564731"},"141":{"question":"300020050100000400780000000203040089000100072007060000501800200048900030000005001","answer":"364721958125389467789456123213547689456198372897263514531874296648912735972635841"},"142":{"question":"005000000100050080000100206000300800050001020009720030000000978040080001806007302","answer":"235678419164259783978134256612345897357891624489726135521463978743982561896517342"},"143":{"question":"009000300005068470000000005000000800506000000090000500000070000000004650964580702","answer":"149257368235168479678349125412735896586491237793826541351672984827914653964583712"},"144":{"question":"000000000000000000600340025200000798000890006800000514001600900000000850038075602","answer":"124567389359218467687349125213456798475891236896723514541682973762934851938175642"},"145":{"question":"000090004000050000000000000200400000050000020900003001340002900000934670700080503","answer":"125396784438157269679248135213465897854719326967823451346572918581934672792681543"},"146":{"question":"009100000000000000400009106000060890060800000095004060030002970000010000900080610","answer":"259136487176428359483759126714265893362891745895374261531642978628917534947583612"},"147":{"question":"009060008130000000600100200002000000000090307000000100500000703060002001900007052","answer":"249763518135248679678159234312475896456891327897326145521984763764532981983617452"},"148":{"question":"007020041020000000000000236004000000065007004098000000001600000800900002042080050","answer":"387526941426139578519478236134265897265897314798314625951642783873951462642783159"},"149":{"question":"000000028000000000000006040103060800450000013800010000048000062062800000070020500","answer":"614357928239148657785296341193462875456789213827513496548931762962875134371624589"},"150":{"question":"000000000023000078400208030000000000305090000000104005001000940002043050040010020","answer":"158379264923461578467258139214835697385697412796124385531782946672943851849516723"},"151":{"question":"080000200000108060500000000100000806006890000700026005000600000000015983800930620","answer":"381469257247158369569273148132547896456891732798326415913682574624715983875934621"},"152":{"question":"030000000005000000009050004000400090000001000090270140040086900060004083070030001","answer":"134627859685149237729358614213465798457891326896273145341586972962714583578932461"},"153":{"question":"000081300004000000000000000200465000000000000089020000320670000040902000060010432","answer":"592781346134256789678349125213465897456897213789123564321674958845932671967518432"},"154":{"question":"090002100024057009500009000003000000007600000000003050000000000040930000902781043","answer":"396842175124357689578169234213475896457698312689213457731524968845936721962781543"},"155":{"question":"650039800003408560700050100000000000300000200000002000400700080002000003078610402","answer":"654139827123478569789256134215347698346891275897562341431725986562984713978613452"},"156":{"question":"070040000000060000000008000000000009000097210007004300031000047005416903942080060","answer":"173245698829361475564978132416832759358697214297154386631529847785416923942783561"},"157":{"question":"700000000004100000060200170000050007400008002870002000000807940040000780907000001","answer":"712384569594176238368295174236451897459768312871932456623817945145629783987543621"},"158":{"question":"004007000120000789700000000203000007050000030000000054502090860001002075070061000","answer":"364987512125346789789125346213458697456279138897613254532794861641832975978561423"},"159":{"question":"080005400000060080000000026023400090000000001700210005300500000000600050005870310","answer":"286135479457962183931748526123456798569387241748219635372591864814623957695874312"},"160":{"question":"040012000003050000070000000000006000000090000800004000431085060702040803005600402","answer":"546312789193758246278469135317826594654197328829534671431285967762941853985673412"},"161":{"question":"080090000000400000570000000005040000300000020700000030431020090850070000060014300","answer":"182596473693487152574132869925348617318769524746251938431825796859673241267914385"},"162":{"question":"000900000000000670009340100012060000000080003090003546500030984643000050070000000","answer":"156972438234158679789346125312465897465789213897213546521637984643891752978524361"},"163":{"question":"001800900035070400700000000020000080506008000090000050000500006600901543004003020","answer":"241835967835679412769214835427156389516398274398427651183542796672981543954763128"},"164":{"question":"004060800000000009000300000010005008056000000709600050000904080043000091067001203","answer":"134269875275148639698357124312475968456892317789613452521934786843726591967581243"},"165":{"question":"000000000023000009008000000000005800050090010890004060030072058005080400902003000","answer":"149236587523817649678459231314765892256398714897124365431672958765981423982543176"},"166":{"question":"007004000000000070000257004003000000400000007700000000000940702064020001070080306","answer":"127364589645198273389257164253479618416835927798612435831946752564723891972581346"},"167":{"question":"000000600000067000067009130010000700000000203000000450341800960000030001800001320","answer":"124358697938167542567249138413526789659784213782913456341872965296435871875691324"},"168":{"question":"500084003000000078000123000004000000057090000080000230700000082840000006905000041","answer":"519784623423569178678123495294318567357296814186457239731645982842931756965872341"},"169":{"question":"000002000100000000000100205204030700000000100090000050000040000041920007005870023","answer":"356482971127359648489167235214538796573296184698714352732645819841923567965871423"},"170":{"question":"050000006100050000400008005200037600300009014000004000007002901000015000900703000","answer":"752391486183456279469278135214537698378629514695184327537842961826915743941763852"},"171":{"question":"007800000000050000000470000210500600000100000700000000041680970000904800000012306","answer":"127863459436259187589471263213547698895126734764398521341685972672934815958712346"},"172":{"question":"000000064005000000000007000000050700000098002090310000030075801578920043901004000","answer":"217583964345269178689147325823456719156798432794312586432675891578921643961834257"},"173":{"question":"390210070000608000000040000000450000000090003009003450530000984007000560900004001","answer":"394215678125678349678349125213456897456897213789123456531762984847931562962584731"},"174":{"question":"000000000000000000000039260000000807300000105570004020001500004702003601890001730","answer":"123468579968257413457139268216395847384726195579814326631572984742983651895641732"},"175":{"question":"000200000100070000579000003000040000007000036000700400000000807062084051080030042","answer":"436215789128379564579468123691843275847521936253796418314652897762984351985137642"},"176":{"question":"080000000000000080400200005200300090006700412708004050531000060600001000040900501","answer":"182457639975613284463289175214365798356798412798124356531842967629571843847936521"},"177":{"question":"060100500030040000789050020000060000407800000000000405501000780003670050006500040","answer":"264187539135249678789356124312465897457891263698723415521934786843672951976518342"},"178":{"question":"040000000030000009000007000200450060006000000800002054024010000000900006901870503","answer":"142369785637185249598247631219458367456731892873692154324516978785923416961874523"},"179":{"question":"000000075000000080000045000100006000000009003098000254001590007000031942004070500","answer":"213968475456127389789345126132456798547289613698713254321594867875631942964872531"},"180":{"question":"000001000103000000070300000000630700006000215080005063000706902050000000900000301","answer":"248961537193457826675328149521634798436879215789215463314786952852193674967542381"},"181":{"question":"000002070004050000508000000003070800050600000080013000000520000045936701900700503","answer":"136842975274159386598367142623475819451698237789213654367521498845936721912784563"},"182":{"question":"060000310130000009000000200310065090000000100000002006000000004073941000948023060","answer":"264759318135284679789136245312465897456897123897312456521678934673941582948523761"},"183":{"question":"007009000020000000000000000000006097005002046008017005000760000702900650006200700","answer":"137529468524638971689174532241356897375892146968417325453761289712983654896245713"},"184":{"question":"200000000130006000060170030000005090000789010008000400000043000000097500905000640","answer":"254938167137256984869174235312465798546789312798312456621543879483697521975821643"},"185":{"question":"060028000020000089008009005000500090050802000000000050030000000000201960980003500","answer":"569128347123457689478369125812534796657892431394716258236975814745281963981643572"},"186":{"question":"040070902000000008000000030020405080000090010000010060300080000504031020980006041","answer":"641378952235149678798652134123465789456897213879213465312784596564931827987526341"},"187":{"question":"206800050000000600000000020000000060000000200090003540001000085060041790000082300","answer":"216834957457129638389657124142795863635418279798263541921376485863541792574982316"},"188":{"question":"300670000024000000000000000200000890000000000098000060600704000072001040040580703","answer":"315672489724198356869345172236457891157869234498213567683724915572931648941586723"},"189":{"question":"060800002100400500000120060005040000000000020080000600000902056000000080852007000","answer":"364859172128476539579123468215648397643791825987235614431982756796514283852367941"},"190":{"question":"000007050000000070009006000203000807000000320008000000030000082862090740974032000","answer":"126387459345129678789456231213645897457918326698273514531764982862591743974832165"},"191":{"question":"300100900000300500060078000000006000050007200097013450000004000000000045940000307","answer":"324165978178329564569478123213546789456897231897213456631754892782931645945682317"},"192":{"question":"000900103000006709000130000000005000056000302000000050000040070843007600900020530","answer":"285974163134256789679138245312465897456789312798312456521643978843597621967821534"},"193":{"question":"030000120000350070000000000000000006000800007080200050301500900502000080000002513","answer":"435678129126359478798124635213795846654813297987246351341587962562931784879462513"},"194":{"question":"000800100000000000070100006200005007000090201080000060001600900607501002840907000","answer":"324876159156249783978153426213465897465798231789312564531624978697581342842937615"},"195":{"question":"000000000000000000070000020010065090050080200090100405000000070040030950080672314","answer":"123546789568297143479318526312465897654789231897123465231954678746831952985672314"},"196":{"question":"000701300000250009000000100302005006000890000009030005000500000000907500000623080","answer":"294761358136258479578349162312475896457896213689132745921584637863917524745623981"},"197":{"question":"030049060006000070000000030020000090400800006000000000012004957000903040004002000","answer":"135749268246138579789256134521467893493825716678391425312684957857913642964572381"},"198":{"question":"000000000130006000600050000000005090050000000060000050306010978580037002790602500","answer":"245173689138296745679458123412365897853749216967821354326514978581937462794682531"},"199":{"question":"200940800130008500000000000300400090050020000008100000000690083000003062900000001","answer":"275941836134268579689357124312475698456829317798136245521694783847513962963782451"},"200":{"question":"501003000000000000600050000000400700050708000090300006310804090800901073040000001","answer":"521643987473189562689257134136492758254768319798315246312874695865921473947536821"},"201":{"question":"080019000130200080000300104203000090500001006000000000300080900750000060908102000","answer":"482519637137246589695378124213465798579821346846793215324687951751934862968152473"},"202":{"question":"000040000020000000050209000010056807000007000080900300000004701040730900901025000","answer":"136548279429173568758269134213456897594387612687912345362894751845731926971625483"},"203":{"question":"007080000003000700060309100210000890000000070700004050000000008001960507075003402","answer":"127586349593241786468379125216735894354698271789124653632457918841962537975813462"},"204":{"question":"600800000000300009500000300210000000000008123000200004001002008760000000082504070","answer":"623819457147325869598476312214937586975648123836251794451762938769183245382594671"},"205":{"question":"000000090000109560000200000003070600000001203000020405000000050500000020908512346","answer":"124356798387149562659287134213475689845691273796823415432768951561934827978512346"},"206":{"question":"000000002000058070670020008010300006065200047007000200000000700000000900986000023","answer":"158437692392658174674129538219374856865291347437586219543962781721843965986715423"},"207":{"question":"600000005000007600000000130000400000000091000090603451300002900060980503001030740","answer":"612349875435817629879265134126458397543791268798623451354172986267984513981536742"},"208":{"question":"059000401000000000460000000000370090000001020000024070000740000600000710980516042","answer":"259637481173482569468159237812375694734961825596824173321748956645293718987516342"},"209":{"question":"000100000003050700070000100004360000000800000098000000001002008705080002980673500","answer":"246137859813956724579248136124365987657829413398714265431592678765481392982673541"},"210":{"question":"009000006030100070560409023103000000400000000890210000301050900600000054000000002","answer":"719325486234168579568479123123546798456987231897213645341852967682791354975634812"},"211":{"question":"000000600020000080060000020213400000406000200700000400000820000070930042090604501","answer":"134258679527169384968347125213486957456793218789512463341825796675931842892674531"},"212":{"question":"000020000030009000000308020120000700050000000090000400000000065000031840082605017","answer":"415726938238419576679358124126594783854173692793862451341987265567231849982645317"},"213":{"question":"007000200100000700400000000200000000000010002090000305600042908840903000070081504","answer":"357164289126598743489237651231475896568319472794826315615742938842953167973681524"},"214":{"question":"000005200200100780070200000000400008006800007807002000001080900000501800080020500","answer":"138675249245139786679248315352417698496853127817962453521386974764591832983724561"},"215":{"question":"001000000004000500570360000003056000000090000000010050007600985042000000060081042","answer":"231548679684179523579362418123456897458297136796813254317624985842935761965781342"},"216":{"question":"000000600030006009009000000003005000050089030008200006000000000045690070067832504","answer":"172958643534126789689347125213465897456789231798213456321574968845691372967832514"},"217":{"question":"000000000000000070780050000000000000006000012807300005000571000501984703978003501","answer":"123467958659138274784259136215846397346795812897312465432571689561984723978623541"},"218":{"question":"980000000103080007000023080000000000006000000000050000400867002602000870009010004","answer":"984175236123486597567923481241638759356749128798251643435867912612394875879512364"},"219":{"question":"000000000020006000009020005200008000340001008800000000001082006060900803070613400","answer":"153849267724156389689327145215738694346591728897264531531482976462975813978613452"},"220":{"question":"207000003100000009009000240000405000450000000700012000000000908040006520000820300","answer":"267149853134258679589367241312485796456793182798612435623574918841936527975821364"},"221":{"question":"800000000000000080060008004205034090000009005000010460000500000680103500902040600","answer":"813426759427951386569378124275634891146789235398215467731562948684193572952847613"},"222":{"question":"070000060005000080000050004002400807000090210000100400000600008807009030003072000","answer":"174283569235946781689751324312465897458397216796128453521634978847519632963872145"},"223":{"question":"000100000020000009400000056004060090000800000600724010031000000000080020080573601","answer":"365197284827456139419238756174365892253819467698724315531642978746981523982573641"},"224":{"question":"019040800000060000000009000103005600000800000090200000000007900005920003002634700","answer":"319742856254168379678359124123475698547896231896213547431587962765921483982634715"},"225":{"question":"005000000100000000609008000000400689000001030000023400000030800043000052900002341","answer":"235146978184297563679358124312475689458961237796823415521734896843619752967582341"},"226":{"question":"008000003000400060507000100000000897000800000080024000401002900602000000070000601","answer":"148569273293417568567238149324156897716893452985724316431672985652981734879345621"},"227":{"question":"070000003100059000000000000000065000050890000800020060600000097003000000905710302","answer":"274681953138259476569374128312465789456897231897123564641532897723948615985716342"},"228":{"question":"070000000000467009000000100000000000300000000008102000000074062040953800087010403","answer":"273591648815467239469328175126735984354689721798142356931874562642953817587216493"},"229":{"question":"000200040004178069500000023100500000050000001009000400312000000600001000800720600","answer":"961235748234178569578469123123546897456897231789312456312684975647951382895723614"},"230":{"question":"900000400000000780400100200200000000368000500500000063030002070005010000000903051","answer":"923578416156234789487196235219365847368741592574829163631452978895617324742983651"},"231":{"question":"580000000000000070070100008000000000450800320700000000301080900800900030000013580","answer":"582347169194658273673129458239476815456891327718532694361785942825964731947213586"},"232":{"question":"000007092020000008000000130000465780000800003090000000500902040084000001002080007","answer":"138547692426391578759628134213465789645879213897213465571932846384756921962184357"},"233":{"question":"002000100030000000000009000003050807458700062609000000001605080705900600906800000","answer":"592348176134567928867129435213456897458791362679283514341675289785912643926834751"},"234":{"question":"000008000230000080000000005023009600400000390090000450002005060000013027078004010","answer":"145268739239457186687391245823549671451786392796132458312875964564913827978624513"},"235":{"question":"400009000000000000609107000000000000000091000708000001301804926000010070900035014","answer":"412359687537468192689127345143582769265791438798643251351874926824916573976235814"},"236":{"question":"000608010020007009000120000000000700307000100800001004430005000000000040960730501","answer":"543698217126457839789123456614382795357946182892571364431265978275819643968734521"},"237":{"question":"680000000000009000070060105000500080000007000000204300500000900840003561001045800","answer":"682351497135479628479862135214536789396187254758294316563718942847923561921645873"},"238":{"question":"007204000100000670008100000000400006000000000000003401340010980091000042870040060","answer":"537264819124389675968157234283491756419576328756823491342615987691738542875942163"},"239":{"question":"070003000034000000009000030020000000400000003000010050010504968860000042940028001","answer":"172453689534869127689172435721345896456987213398216754217534968863791542945628371"},"240":{"question":"000000200003060580050009007010050000000091000009720010530000970700003850000070031","answer":"146587293973162584258439167317854629625391748489726315531248976764913852892675431"},"241":{"question":"200000000130000000000300100000065890000089060090700000021000630040630900003070010","answer":"254196378136827459789354126372465891415289763698713245921548637547631982863972514"},"242":{"question":"000500800000000000000040005020400700000800000800000456001004970000031004904705630","answer":"132567849465198327798243165523416798647859213819372456351684972276931584984725631"},"243":{"question":"000300020000000000000208104000475809006090000097010052000000000000004000985000041","answer":"148357926263149578579268134312475869456892317897613452624581793731924685985736241"},"244":{"question":"002000000000070000709000020210006008500000003690020000000084675000030000970000300","answer":"132458796456279831789613524217346958548197263693825147321984675865732419974561382"},"245":{"question":"000000807130008009500060003310040000050090300080300204000004000003000902005000400","answer":"246139857137258649598467123312746598654892371789315264921684735463571982875923416"},"246":{"question":"000000000000000009400009000004000790000098210000024300030046070600900020901500003","answer":"129453687863217549475689132214365798356798214798124356532846971647931825981572463"},"247":{"question":"900000400000000500000080006210056000075090000009000005500008907046900000090073641","answer":"923165478168437592457289136214356789375891264689724315531648927746912853892573641"},"248":{"question":"000100020000008000000060004000470806000020010790010000005701980040030050001002063","answer":"357194628426358179189267534213475896564829317798613245635741982842936751971582463"},"249":{"question":"690508300004009000070000000000056890006000000700002000007601000060920000900700010","answer":"691548372234179568578263149312456897456897231789312456847631925163925784925784613"},"250":{"question":"600040800000000000009000120023000000000000007790000002002580706860000500045000281","answer":"631245879258179364479368125123497658584612937796853412312584796867921543945736281"},"251":{"question":"000000500000000009000000000000500000456700231090210056001020907600931000980000302","answer":"123896574765342189849157623217563498456789231398214756531428967672931845984675312"},"252":{"question":"000000000020400000000000008210300000000801000780020035605000004800900502000006013","answer":"143258679928467351567139248214375896356891427789624135635712984871943562492586713"},"253":{"question":"000002350000050009000000000010000000300080100000600520430090000005840902081000400","answer":"147962358263158749859374216514729683326485197798613524432596871675841932981237465"},"254":{"question":"000000020103008000050070006000506807300007004080004300007000000600900003000003041","answer":"469315728173268459258479136924536817315897264786124395537641982641982573892753641"},"255":{"question":"209003008000050000078100200000075000400000000000000400500030084700082003000510700","answer":"259743168146258379378169245631475892425891637897326451512637984764982513983514726"},"256":{"question":"269000001130208000000000206010000000000000100000000460601003900083045000905001300","answer":"269354781137268549458179236314596827876432195592817463621783954783945612945621378"},"257":{"question":"000160000100008009080000100010040090458090000096000000000000980001903000000000061","answer":"234169578165278439987354126312546897458792613796831245523617984641983752879425361"},"258":{"question":"006300000000058600009000034004000000357000000000010020000040002002071063960803410","answer":"176394258423158679589762134214539786357286941698417325731645892842971563965823417"},"259":{"question":"700000000020000009689000000200000097000000010000003000301602050560000002070038600","answer":"713249586425186379689357124236815497857964213194723865341672958568491732972538641"},"260":{"question":"000600000100000400780200030000000000057098300000720500000000075870904000000000841","answer":"234619758165873429789245136428531697657498312913726584346182975871954263592367841"},"261":{"question":"067000000024300000080040000000056090000000000006800410030000704805000901940175080","answer":"167289345524361879389547162413756298798412536256893417631928754875634921942175683"},"262":{"question":"006000100004000000000020000200065000007000000090003400000500060840602901900871500","answer":"326947158174358296589126347213465789457289613698713425731594862845632971962871534"},"263":{"question":"900004000030000000000000000100000000000007000000210456302608910690042070875031002","answer":"916324587238756194457189263124865739563497821789213456342678915691542378875931642"},"264":{"question":"000074000230000000000200030100000000008000003070000005312548976000000300000907021","answer":"561374289234189567789256134145763892628495713973812645312548976497621358856937421"},"265":{"question":"085000000000400080009000000010000000006700020800000006500800900008002015902571803","answer":"185237469623419587479658231214396758396785124857124396541863972738942615962571843"},"266":{"question":"000100000020000009000409000014050800000007200007204000000623905000900741080700600","answer":"349162578126578439758439162214356897563897214897214356471623985632985741985741623"},"267":{"question":"900000000100060000560000000000000008046090015780000300431000907657901002800000000","answer":"923145786174368529568729431219453678346897215785216394431582967657931842892674153"},"268":{"question":"030000005025340600080006000013000000450007010000000406040000007000971340900004001","answer":"634718295125349678789526134813465729456297813297183456341652987568971342972834561"},"269":{"question":"000000096200060000000000023020040000000000001908003200000684007000901632090005010","answer":"134527896279368145856419723521746389743892561968153274312684957485971632697235418"},"270":{"question":"081000070300107200079008000000070000050090307090603001000000008830900002000000000","answer":"281349576345167289679528134163274895452891367798653421516732948834916752927485613"},"271":{"question":"000300000000070000700050023000500800007000200090200700300060902060920007900831600","answer":"124386579539172468786459123213547896457698231698213745341765982865924317972831654"},"272":{"question":"000070090005000000600300020000065009050090200000020006000004007567032800984010000","answer":"123576498475289613698341725241765389856193274739428156312854967567932841984617532"},"273":{"question":"000005200000000000000230005000000897057001020060007000002570000000900730704683000","answer":"136745289528169473479238165241356897857491326963827541392574618685912734714683952"},"274":{"question":"400000050000300060009450003000500008047080000000100000301294006000013005074005300","answer":"413628759285379164769451283132547698647982531598136427351294876826713945974865312"},"275":{"question":"340600010000000000000000040003000097450708000800200056001000900000001080082060000","answer":"345629718127384569698175243213546897456798321879213456561832974734951682982467135"},"276":{"question":"090204070000000000050000200000000708065090120009010060008020907001900002900800003","answer":"193254876246187539857639241312546798765398124489712365638421957571963482924875613"},"277":{"question":"070008000000000480480000060004006708007200000000000000000090800865004920000835070","answer":"172468359356729481489351267234516798597283146618947532743692815865174923921835674"},"278":{"question":"008300000020400000406709003004007098060000000879000305500002000607000000000000501","answer":"198325467723416859456789123214537698365198274879264315531942786647851932982673541"},"279":{"question":"000004000045060078000000000100000009450300000090000300500006003034021007907000020","answer":"216784935345169278789235164173642589452398716698517342521476893834921657967853421"},"280":{"question":"000001000003006000460000020200000000050090007000004013600000000702680900080712406","answer":"527341698893256174461978325238167549154893267976524813615439782742685931389712456"},"281":{"question":"000082000020000000000000030214030000300090010080710002702840000801900000005001020","answer":"143682579529173486678459231214538967357296814986714352762845193831927645495361728"},"282":{"question":"000640000100080000400000080000000008300700024700000000000070040805900276000460850","answer":"238641597157289463469357182594126738381795624726834915612578349845913276973462851"},"283":{"question":"000200004000000570000000000000006000000001000008000415002018953000970001000534820","answer":"156287394234169578879345162315426789497851236628793415742618953583972641961534827"},"284":{"question":"000000070030000080000040035100400700450080000000002006000801007700000040060074023","answer":"214358679537169284698247135126435798459786312873912456342891567785623941961574823"},"285":{"question":"750008930000000000000300004203475000005800010090000000000584701500920003040000800","answer":"751248936324169578986357124213475689465892317897613245632584791578921463149736852"},"286":{"question":"005907000004000080000000040000000000006080000700213000001092070560070030900604500","answer":"185947263324156789697328145813765492256489317749213658431592876562871934978634521"},"287":{"question":"000010000120400000007009020000000708300798000098000000000006072002900603006250000","answer":"435812967129467835687539421261345798354798216798621354943186572512974683876253149"},"288":{"question":"270000001100000000500000200002000000050000000090300000021000050040901080003645012","answer":"274536891138279465569418237312864579456197328897352146621783954745921683983645712"},"289":{"question":"005000604040039500000050100020547000050000000000002400000004000064000750002065001","answer":"135278694246139578789456123321547869458691237697382415513724986864913752972865341"},"290":{"question":"705040002000580067000000100000306700050008200007000000530600000000901000000035640","answer":"765143892123589467489267135214356789356798214897412356531624978648971523972835641"},"291":{"question":"000002037023000080000000000200036000300000000000020350401005002097041800060903410","answer":"145682937623197584789354621258436179376519248914728356431865792597241863862973415"},"292":{"question":"009200000004050700508000000000065007000090000800023000005600900000000502900537641","answer":"139274856264358719578916234321865497456791328897423165715642983643189572982537641"},"293":{"question":"000010064000060009070000005000000090000000200080003006020634087864000002037000040","answer":"253719864148265379679348125312456798496187253785923416921634587864571932537892641"},"294":{"question":"000000070000100008780200000100050000005008000000000050500060000030081527970020060","answer":"213845679456179238789236145142357896365498712897612354521764983634981527978523461"},"295":{"question":"000040070100060000000000005010000700000090040008400000031000067740950010980703020","answer":"253148679179365482864279135415682793327591846698437251531824967742956318986713524"},"296":{"question":"000008000000000000600104000000000006450801703007036000341500007000010084000007000","answer":"123658479574293168689174235932745816456821793817936542341589627765312984298467351"},"297":{"question":"800000502003500000000200000010300080000000010000010060030680947040020801900745020","answer":"864137592123594678579268134412356789396872415758419263235681947647923851981745326"},"298":{"question":"010000032004000080080030100000460800000000000000700005005621000801907000000083610","answer":"516874932234159786789236154123465879457398261698712345375621498861947523942583617"},"299":{"question":"000000000000209560009000003010000000000800030008000456020080000540000807980005002","answer":"132567984874239561659148273315496728467852139298371456721684395546923817983715642"}}};
